[
    {
        "question": "Sailor Moon) Which two Sailor Senshi are lesbian lovers?",
        "answers": ["Sailor Uranus and Sailor Neptune"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) Usagi Tsukino is better known as?",
        "answers": ["Sailor Moon"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) Which superhero franchise inspired Sailor Moon?",
        "answers": ["Super Sentai"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Moon the soldier of?",
        "answers": ["Love and Justice"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Mercury the soldier of?",
        "answers": ["Water"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Mars the soldier of?",
        "answers": ["Fire"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Jupiter the soldier of?",
        "answers": ["Thunder"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Venus the soldier of?",
        "answers": ["Beauty"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Pluto the soldier of?",
        "answers": ["Spacetime"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Uranus the soldier of?",
        "answers": ["Sky"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Neptune the soldier of?",
        "answers": ["Ocean"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Saturn the soldier of?",
        "answers": ["Destruction"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) Who is the oldest Sailor Senshi?",
        "answers": ["Sailor Pluto"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What does the Japanese title translate to?",
        "answers": ["Pretty Soldier Sailor Moon"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) How many episodes does the original Sailor Moon have?",
        "answers": ["200 episodes"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) How many animated films were there?",
        "answers": ["3 films"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) Which other magic girl Sailor Moon shares an animation team with Sailor Moon?",
        "answers": ["Revolutionary Girl Utena"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What does Usagi Tsukino translate to?",
        "answers": ["Rabbit on the moon"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What hair color did Sailor Moon originally have?",
        "answers": ["Pink"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Uranus' helicopter's name?",
        "answers": ["Tenoumaru"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Neptune's helicopter's name?",
        "answers": ["Kaiohmaru"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) Which Sailor Scout was the only one to awaken completely on her own?",
        "answers": ["Sailor Neptune"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) Which company was interested in acquiring the rights to Sailor Moon in 1997?",
        "answers": ["The Walt Disney Company"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) How many known Sailor Scouts are there?",
        "answers": ["20 Scouts", "Twenty Scouts"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) Which song is Sailor Moon mentioned in?",
        "answers": ["One Week by The Barenaked Ladies"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What make and model is Sailor Uranus' car?",
        "answers": ["A Ferrari 512M", "Ferrari 512M"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) Which Sailor Scout was the most popular in Japan?",
        "answers": ["Sailor Mercury"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) Which character gets themself kidnapped the most often?",
        "answers": ["Tuxedo Mask"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) Which villain was the only one to die twice in the Sailor Moon?",
        "answers": ["Kaolinite"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sailor Moon) What is Sailor Mercury allergic to?",
        "answers": ["Love letters"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) Which of these species resembles birds?",
        "answers": ["Silgrians"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) Which assassin lead the Anten Seven?",
        "answers": ["Hitoriga"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) What fighting style was used by Iraga?",
        "answers": ["Hoke Shadow Boxing"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) What ship component does dragonite fuel?",
        "answers": ["Munchousen Drive"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) 'Tao Magic' is the short way to say what?",
        "answers": ["Senjutsu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) How many times do we see Aisha successfully transform into her beast form?",
        "answers": ["Two"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) Counting him, how many men were in CrackerJack's gang?",
        "answers": ["5 Men", "five men"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) What is the name of the spaceship piloted by Gene Starwind?",
        "answers": ["Outlaw Star"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) What is the operating system for the Outlaw Star?",
        "answers": ["Gilliam II"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) What species is Aisha Clan Clan?",
        "answers": ["Ctarl-Ctarl", "Ctarl Ctarl"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Outlaw Star) What is the first caster shell Gene Starwind used?",
        "answers": ["#3", "Number 3"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad) What type of guitar did Ryusuke lend to Koyuki?",
        "answers": ["Gibson Les Paul"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad) What song does Maho and Yukio sing together in the pool?",
        "answers": ["Moon on the water"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad) What Beatles song does Yukio sing at the Greatful Sounds Music Festival?",
        "answers": ["I've Got A Feeling"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad) Ryusuke owns a dog, what is his name?",
        "answers": ["Beck"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad) What postion is Saku in Beck?",
        "answers": ["Drummer"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad) What postion is Ray in Beck?",
        "answers": ["Lead Guitarist"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad) What postion is Chiba in Beck?",
        "answers": ["Main Vocalist"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad) What postion is Taira in Beck?",
        "answers": ["Bass Guitarist"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad) Who is the main protaganist of Beck?",
        "answers": ["Yukio Tanaka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad) Whats the opening theme for Beck) Mongolian Chop Squad?",
        "answers": ["Hit in the USA"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What anime does Kurisu's online name reference?",
        "answers": ["Dragon Ball Z", "DBZ"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is written on the Lab Members badge?",
        "answers": ["OSHMKUFA 2010"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) Who does Mayuri work for?",
        "answers": ["Faris"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is Mayuri's favorite hobby?",
        "answers": ["Cosplay"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) How old is Mayuri Shiina?",
        "answers": ["16 Years"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) Who ate Kurisu's pudding?",
        "answers": ["Rintaro Okabe", "Rintaro", "Okabe"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) How old is Rintaro Okabe?",
        "answers": ["18 Years"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What will happen to Mayuri when Mayuri's pocket watch stops working?",
        "answers": ["Death", "Dies", "die", "She dies"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) Who is the sixth person that is shown in the opening?",
        "answers": ["Rintaro Okabe", "Rintaro", "Okabe"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is the name of Okabe's Laboratory?",
        "answers": ["Future Gadget Laboratory"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What name does Okabe call Kurisu?",
        "answers": ["Christina"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) In what area of Tokyo does Steins;Gate take place?",
        "answers": ["Akihabara"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) Why does Mayuri stay with Okabe?",
        "answers": ["She's his hostage", "Hostage"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is Rintaro's landlord's name?",
        "answers": ["Yugo", "Mr Braun"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is Okabe's favorite drink?",
        "answers": ["Dk Pepper"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) Steins;Gate is a collaboration work between 5pb. and who?",
        "answers": ["Nitro+"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What does the team call the text messages sent to the past?",
        "answers": ["Dmail", "d-mail"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What nickname does Rintaro give to Moeka?",
        "answers": ["Shining Finger"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is the name of the ability to retain memories across world lines?",
        "answers": ["Reading Steiner"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) Who was Black Rock Shooter's counterpart?",
        "answers": ["Mato Kuroi", "Kuroi Mato"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) Who was Dead Master's counterpart?",
        "answers": ["Yomi Takanashi", "Takanashi Yomi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) Who was Strength's counterpart?",
        "answers": ["Yuu Koutari", "Koutari Yuu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) Who was Chariot's counterpart?",
        "answers": ["Kagari Izuriha", "Kagari", "Izuriha Kagari"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) What color of macaron did Kagari give to Yomi and herself?",
        "answers": ["Pretty-Colored", "Yellow and Pink", "Pink and Yellow"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) What color of macarons did Kagari give to Mato?",
        "answers": ["Dirty-Colored", "Brown"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) What color of macaron did Kagari give to herself?",
        "answers": ["Yellow"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) What does Chariot shoot?",
        "answers": ["Macaron's"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) What does Dead Master weild?",
        "answers": ["Scythe"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) Near the end of Black Rock Shooter what does Kuroi Mato see?",
        "answers": ["Rainbow", "All Colors"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) What book does Kuroi Mato enjoy the most?",
        "answers": ["The Tiny Bird & The Colors", "The Tiny Bird"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) What color are sneezes referred to in the book that Kuroi Mato enjoys?",
        "answers": ["Pink"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) What does the bird do at the end of The Tiny Bird & The Colors?",
        "answers": ["dies"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) Who was Black Gold Saw's counterpart?",
        "answers": ["Saya Irino", "Irino Saya", "Saya", "Irino"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) Who was the captain of the basketball club?",
        "answers": ["Arata Kohata", "Arata", "Kohata Arata"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) Who did the captian of the basketball club confess to?",
        "answers": ["Takuu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) When did the first episode of the anime air?",
        "answers": ["February 2012"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) When did the OVA air?",
        "answers": ["July 2010"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) What sport club did Yomi join?",
        "answers": ["Volleyball"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Rock Shooter) What was the shape of the phone charm that Mato bought for Yomi?",
        "answers": ["A Star", "Star "]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Chrno Crusade) Who did Chrono kill by an accident?",
        "answers": ["Mary Magdelene"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Chrno Crusade) Who is Rosette's brother?",
        "answers": ["Joshua Christopher"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Chrno Crusade) How old was Rosette when she met Chrono?",
        "answers": ["12 years old"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Chrno Crusade) How many apostles are there?",
        "answers": ["Seven"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Chrno Crusade) Who is the Main protaganist?",
        "answers": ["Rosette Christopher"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Chrno Crusade) What occupation is Rosette?",
        "answers": ["Exorcist"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Chrno Crusade) Who does Rosette work for?",
        "answers": ["Magdalene Order", "Order of Magdelene"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Chrno Crusade) Who is Chrono's brother?",
        "answers": ["Aion"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Chrno Crusade) Where was Chrono Born?",
        "answers": ["Pandaemonium"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Chrno Crusade) What does Rosette use as a seal for Chrono?",
        "answers": ["Pocket Watch"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is the internet called in the show?",
        "answers": ["The Wired"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is the full name for the main protaganist?",
        "answers": ["Lain Iwakura", "Iwakura Lain"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) Who is Lain's Sister?",
        "answers": ["Mika Iwakura", "Iwakura Mika", "Mika"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 1?",
        "answers": ["Weird"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 2?",
        "answers": ["Girls"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 3?",
        "answers": ["Psyche"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 4?",
        "answers": ["Religion"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 5?",
        "answers": ["Distortion"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 6?",
        "answers": ["Kids"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 7?",
        "answers": ["Society"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 8?",
        "answers": ["Rumors"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 9?",
        "answers": ["Protocol"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 10?",
        "answers": ["Love"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 11?",
        "answers": ["Infornography"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 12?",
        "answers": ["Landscape"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Layer 13?",
        "answers": ["Ego"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Lains first computer?",
        "answers": ["Navi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What did Lain consume in Layer 2?",
        "answers": ["Accela"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is the Opening song called?",
        "answers": ["Duvet"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is the techno club called in the show?",
        "answers": ["Cyberia"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What costume does Lain wear to bed?",
        "answers": ["Bear costume"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What was Copland OS based off of in real life?",
        "answers": ["Apple", "Apple Computers"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What text-to-speech software does the show use to say Layer## at the beginning?",
        "answers": ["Whisper", "Mac OS text-to-speech"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) Present Day",
        "answers": ["Present Time"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) 'No matter where you are, _______________'",
        "answers": ["we're all connected", "we are all connected"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) Who commits suicide in the first Layer?",
        "answers": ["Chisa Yomoda", "Yomada Chisa", "Chisa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) Who was the only person to kiss Lain?",
        "answers": ["Taro"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) How old is Lain?",
        "answers": ["14 years old"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) Who is the DJ in Cyberia?",
        "answers": ["JJ"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Serial Experiments Lain) What is Lain considered?",
        "answers": ["God"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which pokemon was supposed to be Ash's original starter?",
        "answers": ["Clefairy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which pokemon was named after a dinosaur?",
        "answers": ["Aerodactyl"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) What other character did Ash's original voice actor voice?",
        "answers": ["Delia Ketchum"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which pokemon did they leave out of the original Pokerap?",
        "answers": ["Mew"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which pokemon is the creator's favorite?",
        "answers": ["Poliwhirl"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which legendary pokemon is the only one that Ash hasn't encountered?",
        "answers": ["Raikou"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Who voiced Mewtwo in the first Pokemon movie?",
        "answers": ["Masachika Ichimura"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) What is the first non Pokemon animal that was seen on the show?",
        "answers": ["A worm"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which eeveelution hasn't been owned by either a main or recurring character?",
        "answers": ["Jolteon"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which pokemon does Cilan fear?",
        "answers": ["Purrloin"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which main character was the first to leave the group in the middle of a journey for a period of time?",
        "answers": ["Clemont"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which rival is the only one to nickname their pokemon?",
        "answers": ["Ritchie"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which recurring human character is the first to share their voice actor with a pokemon?",
        "answers": ["Sawyer"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which regular rival is the first to be seen capturing a pokemon and receiving a gym badge on screen?",
        "answers": ["Paul"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which character is the only male to have made it to the Top 4 of the Sinnoh Grand Festival?",
        "answers": ["Nando"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which character had a running gag that involved them chasing their runaway rice ball?",
        "answers": ["Morrison"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which rival has a team made of only eeveelutions?",
        "answers": ["Virgil"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which Unova rival was the only one to encounter Team Rocket?",
        "answers": ["Bianca"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Pokemon) Which former trainer companion is the only one to not have a Pokemon capable of Mega Evolution or a Pokemon that can evolve into one?",
        "answers": ["Cilan"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which genre is aimed at girls between 10-18?",
        "answers": ["shoujo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the first known Japanese animation produced?",
        "answers": ["1917"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The practice of dressing up like anime characters in Japan is called?",
        "answers": ["cosplay"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In yaoi pairing, what is the 'receiving', 'bottom', or passive partner known as?",
        "answers": ["uke"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In yaoi pairing, what is the 'top' or dominant partner known as?",
        "answers": ["seme"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a popular anime/manga character archetype that derives from the Japanese pronunciation of the English word 'cool'?",
        "answers": ["kuudere", "coodere"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a Japanese term for a character development process that describes a person who is initially cold and even hostile towards another person before gradually showing their warm side over time?",
        "answers": ["tsundere"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Type of anime aimed at young boys under the age of fifteen?",
        "answers": ["shonen"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Type of anime aimed at young men between the ages of 15-24?",
        "answers": ["seinen"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Type of anime aimed at adult women?",
        "answers": ["josei"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Type of anime largely focused on one distinct aspect) pilotable robots?",
        "answers": ["mecha"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Type of anime about innocent young girls using a magical object to transform into a superhero version of themselves?",
        "answers": ["magical girl", "mahou shoujo", "majokko"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Type of anime which do not show sexual intercourse or genitalia, but sexual themes are referenced?",
        "answers": ["ecchi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Type of anime where one male character, the protagonist, at the center of a group of female characters who are all vying for his romantic affections?",
        "answers": ["harem"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What character type is a heroine that started as a villain trying to kill the protagonist but then switched to his side after falling in love with him?",
        "answers": ["mayadere"]
    },
    {
        "question": "It's common in anime for a character to pull their lower eyelid down to taunt someone. What is this called?",
        "answers": ["akanabe"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What anime character type is known as a quiet and often antisocial character?",
        "answers": ["dandere(What character type is very loving and gentle to someone before their devotion becomes destructive in nature, often through violence and/or brutality?", "yandere"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What was the first entry of the SAO manga written for?",
        "answers": ["A novel writing contest", "writing contest"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What is the game SAO the first of",
        "answers": ["It's the first virtual reality?", "VRMMORPG"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What is the castle in SAO called?",
        "answers": ["Aincrad"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) How many floors does the castle in SAO have?",
        "answers": ["100 floors"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What button does SAO not allow you to use?",
        "answers": ["The log out button", "log out"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) How many people were killed playing SAO?",
        "answers": ["3853 people"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) How many unique skills are there in Sword Art Online?",
        "answers": ["10 skills"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What novel inspired SAO?",
        "answers": ["Realtime"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What is Kirito's Unique Skill?",
        "answers": ["Dual Blades"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What processor does Kirito's homemade computer use?",
        "answers": ["A 24Ghz", "24Ghz"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What is Asuna's rapier called?",
        "answers": ["Lambent Light"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What is Lizbeth's original hair color?",
        "answers": ["Brown"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What is Kirito's favorite food",
        "answers": ["Teriyaki chicken burgers?", "Teriyaki burgers"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What is Kirito's favorite skill?",
        "answers": ["Fishing"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What year does SAO takes place in?",
        "answers": ["year 2022"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What are the heroes in SAO called?",
        "answers": ["Clearers"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) How long is the period between the death of the player in the game and the death of the player in real life?",
        "answers": ["10 seconds"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What is Kirito's full name?",
        "answers": ["Kirigaya Kazuto", "Kazuto"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What other anime takes place in the same universe as SAO?",
        "answers": ["Accel World"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) Who developed the game Sword Art Online in the Sword Art Online anime?",
        "answers": ["Kayaba Akihiko", "Heathcliff"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) What is the guild that consists of only Player Killers called?",
        "answers": ["The Laughing Coffin", "Laughing Coffin"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) When was Asuna born?",
        "answers": ["September 30th, 2007"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) How old was Kiriko when he first began playing Sword Art Online?",
        "answers": ["14 years old"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) How old was Kiriko when he finishes playing Sword Art Online?",
        "answers": ["16 years old"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) Who was Kirito's in game wife?",
        "answers": ["Yuuki Asuna", "Asuna Yuuki", "Asuna"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sword Art Online) When was Kirito born?",
        "answers": ["October 7th, 2008"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) Reo Kawamura ->",
        "answers": ["Mai Sawaguchi", "Mai"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) Mai Sawaguchi ->",
        "answers": ["Reo Kawamura", "Reo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) Kaede Kitajima ->",
        "answers": ["Sara Kitajima", "Sara"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) Sara Kitajima ->",
        "answers": ["Kaede Kitajima", "Kaede"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) Nanami Oda ->",
        "answers": ["Yuna Matsubara", "Yuna"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) Yuna Matsubara ->",
        "answers": ["Nanami Oda", "Nanami"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) Takako Suminoe ->",
        "answers": ["Runa Horaisen", "Runa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) Runa Horaisen ->",
        "answers": ["Takako Suminoe", "Takako"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) Eris Shitogi ->",
        "answers": ["Shizuku Kirishima", "Shizuku"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) What is Reo Kawamura's dere?",
        "answers": ["Tsundere"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) What is Sara Kitajima's job?",
        "answers": ["Model", "Professional Model"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) What is Sara Kitajima and Kaede Kitajima's family relationship?",
        "answers": ["Cousin"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo) What is Nanami Oda's favorite food?",
        "answers": ["Strawberry"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuki wo) What is the english title?",
        "answers": ["A Kiss for the Petals"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuki wo) What is the School name?",
        "answers": ["St. Micheal's School For Girls", "St. Micheal's"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Bleach) What fruit is also the nickname of Ichigo Kurosaki?",
        "answers": ["Strawberry"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Bleach) How much time does it take for a shinigami to learn how to perform bankai under Kisuke Urahara's method?",
        "answers": ["3 days"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Bleach) Who does Ichigo deeply respect?",
        "answers": ["William Shakespeare"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Bleach) Which character was the first character that the creator created?",
        "answers": ["Rukia Kuchiki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Bleach) Why did Bambietta get the nickname Bastardbine?",
        "answers": ["Her notorious cruelty", "Her cruelty", "Cruelty"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Bleach) Who is the only character that Ichigo has killed?",
        "answers": ["Ginjo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Bleach) Where is Urahara's shop located in?",
        "answers": ["Karakura Town"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Bleach) Which Tove Jansson character inspired Kisuke?",
        "answers": ["Snufkin"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Bleach) What does Ichigo's name mean according to his father?",
        "answers": ["He who protects"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Bleach) What is Ichigo's blood type?",
        "answers": ["A type"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Shingeki no Kyojin) Who is the creator's favorite character?",
        "answers": ["Jean Kirstein"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Shingeki no Kyojin) Which character did Hajame Isayama originally plan to kill off?",
        "answers": ["Sasha Blouse", "Sasha"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Shingeki no Kyojin) How old is Levi?",
        "answers": ["Over 30 years old"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Shingeki no Kyojin) Which two characters' names references an infamous cannibal?",
        "answers": ["Sawney and Bean"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Shingeki no Kyojin) Which character shares its voice actor with the famous vocaloid Hatsune Miku?",
        "answers": ["Ymir"]
    },
    {   
        "question": "(Shingeki no Kyojin) What does Eren's name mean in Turkish?",
        "answers": ["Saint"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Shingeki no Kyojin) Which country blacklisted this anime?",
        "answers": ["China"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Shingeki no Kyojin) What is Mikasa's name taken from",
        "answers": ["A Japanese battleship?", "A Battleship"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Shingeki no Kyojin) How many people do the corps lose when they kill a Titan?",
        "answers": ["30 people"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Shingeki no Kyojin) What is Marco's birthday?",
        "answers": ["June 16th"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Hetalia) What is Italy's birthdate?",
        "answers": ["March 17th "]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Hetalia) Which character was based on a friend of Hidekaz Himaruya?",
        "answers": ["Germany"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Hetalia) Japan was stated to be able to _____ in a Christmas event?",
        "answers": ["Imitate voices"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Hetalia) What is America's human name?",
        "answers": ["Alfred F. Jones"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Hetalia) Which other Himaruya webcomic character is England modeled after?",
        "answers": ["Hikone Katom"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Hetalia) France's most undesirable relationship is with?",
        "answers": ["Spain"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Hetalia) How tall is Russia?",
        "answers": ["5 foot 11 inches"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Hetalia) Which character is immortal?",
        "answers": ["China"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Hetalia) Which character thinks of Spain as an older brother?",
        "answers": ["Italy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Hetalia) South Italy's hair is darker than his brother because he has____ _____",
        "answers": ["Arabic blood"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) Which two villains has Goku killed?",
        "answers": ["Yakon and Kid Buu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) How much money did the Japanese government raise to fun a DBZ movie?",
        "answers": ["50 million yen"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) What gender is Goku's Japanese voice actor?",
        "answers": ["Female"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) What does Bulma's name roughly translates to?",
        "answers": ["Panties"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) Who is Akira Toriyama's favorite character?",
        "answers": ["Piccolo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) What is Goku's mother's name?",
        "answers": ["Gine"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) Which fight was the longest fight in anime history?",
        "answers": ["Goku vs Frieza"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) What does Vegeta fear?",
        "answers": ["Worms"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) Why does Krillin have six dots on his forehead?",
        "answers": ["His training"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) Which character is a baseball player?",
        "answers": ["Yamcha"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(High School of the Dead) Who said) 'No matter how tainted you are, I'll still admire you for as long as I'm alive”?",
        "answers": ["Takashi Komuro", "Takashi", "Kumuro"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(High School of the Dead) Which character is the first to realize that knocking “Them” over is almost as effective as killing them?",
        "answers": ["Saeko Busujima", "Saeko", "Busujima"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(High School of the Dead) Which character was based off of a manga creator?",
        "answers": ["Kohta Hirano", "Kohta", "Hirano"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(High School of the Dead) Who's just learning to ride a bike?",
        "answers": ["Alice Maresato", "Alice", "Maresato"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(High School of the Dead) Which character is the key to the group's survival?",
        "answers": ["Shizuka Marikawa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(High School of the Dead) Who said) “Girls are complex aren't they?”?",
        "answers": ["Rei Miyamoto", "Rei", "Miyamoto"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(High School of the Dead) Who killed Seto?",
        "answers": ["Saya Takagi", "Saya", "Takagi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(High School of the Dead) Who is one of the first to get bitten?",
        "answers": ["Kyoko Hayashi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(High School of the Dead) Who are the two girls that have a noticeable small bust?",
        "answers": ["Misuzu Ichijou and Asami Nakaoka", "Misuzu and Asami", "Ichijou and Nakaoka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(High School of the Dead) Who is one of Koichi Shido's followers?",
        "answers": ["Miku Yuuki", "Miku", "Yuuki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Death Note) Who is the first to find out that Light is Kira?",
        "answers": ["Misa Amane"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Death Note) What is Mello's real name?",
        "answers": ["Mero Mihael Keehl"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Death Note) Which episode does L die in?",
        "answers": ["Episode 25"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Death Note) What rank was Light in high school when he found the death note?",
        "answers": ["Senior"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Death Note) Who was the Shinigami that fell in love with Misa?",
        "answers": ["Gelus"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Death Note) How many humans have used a notebook's pags to kill?",
        "answers": ["Seven"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Death Note) How many days was Light held in solitary confinement by the taskforce?",
        "answers": ["50 days"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Death Note) What was the color of Higuchi's car when he was being chased by Aiber and Mogi?",
        "answers": ["Red"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Death Note) What is L's fighting style?",
        "answers": ["Capoeira"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Soul Eater) Who published Soul Eater?",
        "answers": ["Square Enix", "Yen Press", "Gangan Comics"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Soul Eater) What does Maka's name mean when rearranged?",
        "answers": ["Scythe"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Soul Eater) What is the name of Black Star's weapon partner?",
        "answers": ["Tsubaki Nakatsukasa", "Tsubaki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Soul Eater) What is Death the Kid's blood type?",
        "answers": ["D"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Soul Eater) What is Soul's theme song",
        "answers": ["So Scandalous?", "Scandalous"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Soul Eater) What is the name Tsubaki a reference to",
        "answers": ["The Japanese camellia flower?", "camellia flower"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Soul Eater) What is Liz and Patty's last name a reference to",
        "answers": ["The Thompson submachine gun?", "Thompson"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Soul Eater) Which two ghosts are known as Evil Spirits?",
        "answers": ["Wrath of the Pharaoh and Flying Dutchman", "Flying Dutchman and Wrath of the Pharaoh"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Soul Eater) In the official popularity poll, what rank did Spirit Albarn take?",
        "answers": ["11th rank"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Soul Eater) Who is Asura's weapon partner?",
        "answers": ["Vajra"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Detective Conan) When was Shinichi's first case?",
        "answers": ["On a plane to LA", "plane to LA"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Detective Conan) Where does Shinichi's detective talent come from?",
        "answers": ["His father"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Detective Conan) Which two characters have a fear of ghosts?",
        "answers": ["Ran and Kazuha"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Detective Conan) Which character is left handed?",
        "answers": ["Gin"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Detective Conan) What does Kaito Kid really likes?",
        "answers": ["Chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Detective Conan) When was the first time that Shinichi met Kid?",
        "answers": ["The Clocktower Heist"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Detective Conan) Who is Gosho Aoyama's favorite character?",
        "answers": ["Ran Mouri"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Detective Conan) What pop band has a singer that is Conan's Japanese voice actor?",
        "answers": ["Two Mix"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Detective Conan) What is the poison that Conan swallowed?",
        "answers": ["APTX 4869"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Detective Conan) What is Shinichi's date of birth?",
        "answers": ["May 4th"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What WWII tank country did Anzio Girls High School mainly support?",
        "answers": ["Italy", "Italian"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What WWII tank country did Saunders University High School mainly support?",
        "answers": ["U.S.", "United States", "USA", "US"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What WWII tank country did St. Gloriana Girls High School mainly support?",
        "answers": ["Britan", "Great Britan", "British"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What WWII tank country did Pravda Girls High School mainly support?",
        "answers": ["Russia", "Russian", "USSR"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What WWII tank country did Kuromorimine Girls High School mainly support?",
        "answers": ["German", "Germany", "Nazi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What tank did the Anglerfish Team drive?",
        "answers": ["Panzer IV Ausf.D", "Panzer IV"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What tank did the Turtle Team drive?",
        "answers": ["Panzer 38", "Jagdpanzer 38", "German Panzer 38", "Czech Panzer 38"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What tank did the Hippo Team drive?",
        "answers": ["German StuG. III Ausf.F", "German StuG. III", "StuG. III"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What tank did the Duck Team drive?",
        "answers": ["Type 89"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What tank did the Rabbit Team drive?",
        "answers": ["M3 Lee"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What tank did the Mallard Team drive?",
        "answers": ["Char B-1"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What tank did the Anteater Team drive?",
        "answers": ["Type-3 Chi-Nu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) What tank did the Leopon Team drive?",
        "answers": ["Tiger"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) Who was the Commander of Pravda Girls High School?",
        "answers": ["Katyusha"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) Who was the Commander of Saunders Girls High School?",
        "answers": ["Kay"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) Who was the Commander of St. Gloriana Girls High School?",
        "answers": ["Darjeeling"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) Who was the Commander of Ooarai Girls High School?",
        "answers": ["Miho Nishizumi", "Miho"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) Who was the Commander of Kuromorimine Girls High School?",
        "answers": ["Maho Nishizumi", "Maho"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Girls und Panzer) Who was the Commander of Anzio Girls High School?",
        "answers": ["Anchovy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) What rank is Shiro Amada?",
        "answers": ["Ensign"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) Who fired “the shot that changed history”?",
        "answers": ["Jamil Neate"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) Which two characters are twins?",
        "answers": ["Kira and Cagalli"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) Who is the main character?",
        "answers": ["Garrod Ran", "Judau Ashta", "Kamille Bidan", "Kira Yamato"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) What is the first Gundam activated in the series?",
        "answers": ["Duel"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) Who was the real life person that George de Sand's name is derived from?",
        "answers": ["A French novelist", "George Gabriel Sand"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) What is the name of the ship that Jamil, Garrod. Tiffa, and others all call home?",
        "answers": ["Freeden"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) Where does Mobile Suit Gundam) The 08th MS Team take place?",
        "answers": ["Southeast Asia"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) Who is Kira's best friend that he has to fight against?",
        "answers": ["Athrun Zala"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) What was the first Gundam ever designed?",
        "answers": ["Wing Gundam Zero"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) What does “Kampfer” mean in German?",
        "answers": ["Warrior"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) Why does Shinn want to kill Kira?",
        "answers": ["Kira killed Stellar"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) Who does Shiro fall in love with?",
        "answers": ["Aina Saharin"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) Who is Kamille's love interest for most of Mobile Suit Zeta Gundam?",
        "answers": ["Four Murasame"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Gundam series) Who's Cagalli supposed to marry before Kira interrupts?",
        "answers": ["Yuna Seiran"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Which character can't swim?",
        "answers": ["Yu Kanda", "Kanda Yu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) How old is Yu",
        "answers": ["9 years old?", "19 years old"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Who was Yu's first kiss?",
        "answers": ["Jiji"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Yu is the ____ out of the four according to Hoshino?",
        "answers": ["Dumbest"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Who's the third most popular character?",
        "answers": ["Lavi", "Rabi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Lavi's blood type is?",
        "answers": ["O"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Who does Lavi share a room with?",
        "answers": ["Bookman"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) What is Lavi's occupation?",
        "answers": ["Chronicler"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Who is Komui's younger sister?",
        "answers": ["Lenalee", "Rinari"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Which country is Lenalee's home country?",
        "answers": ["China"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) What is Lenalee's birthday?",
        "answers": ["May 11th"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) How much does Lenalee weigh?",
        "answers": ["106 Lbs"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Which character is ambidextrous",
        "answers": ["Allen Walker?", "Aren Woka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Which holiday is Allen's birthday?",
        "answers": ["Christmas"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) What's Yu's nickname for Allen?",
        "answers": ["Bean sprout"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(D.Gray-Man) Which character is also considered an Earl?",
        "answers": ["Allen", "Aren"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) What is Benny's race?",
        "answers": ["Jewish-American"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) What is Dutch's weapon?",
        "answers": ["A shotgun"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) Rock is a _ ____ turned unwitting pirate of the Black Lagoon?",
        "answers": ["Japanese businessman", "Businessman"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) What is one of the other names that Revy goes by?",
        "answers": ["Rebecca", "Two Hands"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) Who is the leader of the Manisarera Cartel?",
        "answers": ["Abrego"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) Who is a survivor of the Battle of the Atlantic?",
        "answers": ["Wentzel H. Ahbe"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) Which character's real name is Sofiya Pavlovna?",
        "answers": ["Balalaika"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) Who's race is Vietnamese?",
        "answers": ["Bao"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) How is Boris easily identified?",
        "answers": ["A scar on his face"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) The boss of Sun Yee On is?",
        "answers": ["Bai Ji-Shan Chang"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) How did Chin die?",
        "answers": ["He got blown up"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) Which character bears a resemblance to a character in Mobile Suit Gundam Wing?",
        "answers": ["Fernando Garcia Lovelace"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) Who is the boss of Asahi Heavy Industrial?",
        "answers": ["Kageyama"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) Who worked with Shenhua at one time?",
        "answers": ["Leigharch"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Lagoon) Who is affiliated with the Nazis?",
        "answers": ["Lord Alfred"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Who's the oldest member?",
        "answers": ["Mori", "Honey-senpai"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Which member is the last to find out that Haruhi is a girl?",
        "answers": ["Tamaki Suoh"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Who's the youngest member?",
        "answers": ["Kaoru"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Who is only in the anime and not in the manga?",
        "answers": ["Eclair Tonnerre", "Eclair"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) How can one differentiate between the Hiitachin?",
        "answers": ["Their hair parting"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Which two characters fight for Haruhi's hand in marriage?",
        "answers": ["Kyoya and Tamaki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Who has the host of the natural type?",
        "answers": ["Haruhi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Who wants to be Mori's apprentice?",
        "answers": ["Ritsu Kasanoda", "Ritsu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) What is Haruhi afraid of the most?",
        "answers": ["Thunder and lightning"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Which two characters are cousins?",
        "answers": ["Mori and Honey"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Which two characters is Mori very protective of?",
        "answers": ["Haruhi and Honey"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) What are Tamaki's two ethnicities?",
        "answers": ["French and Japanese"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Which character is the first to figure out that Haruhi is a girl?",
        "answers": ["Kyoya"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) When upset or depressed where does Tamaki go?",
        "answers": ["In a corner"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) What kind of business is Kyoya's family in?",
        "answers": ["Medical"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) How did Hideki die?",
        "answers": ["A car crash", "car accident", "car crash"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Who is Hideki's best friend?",
        "answers": ["Ooyama"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Who is the main protagonist of the Heaven's Door manga?",
        "answers": ["Hideki Hinata", "Hinata Hideki", "Hinata"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) What is Yuri's nickname?",
        "answers": ["Yurippe"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Who's last gesture for Kanade was giving her a hug?",
        "answers": ["Yuri's", "Yuri"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) What was Otonashi's reason for living",
        "answers": ["His little sister?", "little sister", "Imouto"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Which other anime character does Otonashi resemble?",
        "answers": ["Kyousuke Natsume", "Kyousuke"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Who wanted to do something in the medical field",
        "answers": ["Yuzuru Otonashi", "Otonashi Yuzuru", "Otonashi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) What does Angel tell Otonashi in the third drama CD?",
        "answers": ["She loves him", "loves him"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) What does the kanji for Kanade mean?",
        "answers": ["To play a tune", "play a tune", "play a song"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) What is Kanade's blood type?",
        "answers": ["A"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Who does Yuri remind Chaa of?",
        "answers": ["His wife"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Who is the fourth member to join the SSS?",
        "answers": ["Chaa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) What is the name of Chaa's English voice actor?",
        "answers": ["Illich Guardiola"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Which character just appears in the anime and not the manga?",
        "answers": ["Fujimaki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Fujimaki can wield these two weapons at the same time?",
        "answers": ["Shirasaya and PPSh41"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Fujimaki can't _____.",
        "answers": ["Swim"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) What does Hisako's name mean?",
        "answers": ["Long lived child"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Which instrument can Hisako play?",
        "answers": ["An electric guitar", "A guitar"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Angel Beats) Which original band member is the only one that doesn't have a surname?",
        "answers": ["Hisako"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) What is John Brown's zodiac sign?",
        "answers": ["Capricorn"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) Who's the cutest male of the group?",
        "answers": ["John Brown", "John"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) What accent does John speak with?",
        "answers": ["Kansai"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) Who will be portrayed in the live action film by Mizuki Yamamoto?",
        "answers": ["Masako Hara", "Misako"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) What is Masako's blood type?",
        "answers": ["AB"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) When was the only time didn't Masako wear a kimono?",
        "answers": ["The last episode"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) Who has a birthday of January 11th?",
        "answers": ["Lin Koujo", "Lin"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) What color is Lin's eyes?",
        "answers": ["Blue", "Gray", "Blue and gray"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) How old is Lin?",
        "answers": ["27 years old"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) Who has a special connection to live trees?",
        "answers": ["Ayako Matsuzaki", "Ayako"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) How tall is Ayako?",
        "answers": ["5 foot 7 inches", "169 cm"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) What is Ayako's occupation?",
        "answers": ["Priestess", "Doctor"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) What is Naru's real name",
        "answers": ["Kazuya Shibuya?", "Oliver Davis"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) Who usually comes to various SPR member's rescue?",
        "answers": ["Naru"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) What is Naru's zodiac sign?",
        "answers": ["Virgo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) What is one name that Houshou Takigawa goes by?",
        "answers": ["Monk", "Bou-san"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) Which character has the O blood type?",
        "answers": ["Houshou Takigawa", "Houshou", "Monk", "Bou-san"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) Who will portray Monk in the live action film?",
        "answers": ["Yosuke Kawamura"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) Who has been attacked the most by spirits?",
        "answers": ["Mai", "Mai Taniyama"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) Who did the author of the series pair Mai with?",
        "answers": ["Naru"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Ghost Hunt) What holiday was Mai born one day before?",
        "answers": ["Fourth of July"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) What is Ciel's title?",
        "answers": ["Earl of Phantomhive"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) Why won't Ciel allow cats in his house?",
        "answers": ["He's allergic", "It would please Sebastian"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) What does Ciel's name mean in French?",
        "answers": ["Sky"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) When did Ciel die?",
        "answers": ["August 26th, 1889"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) What is Ciel's favorite flower?",
        "answers": ["Sterling silver rose"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) Who is Ciel's fiancee?",
        "answers": ["Elizabeth Midford"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) Who does the author and Ciel's voice actor ship him with?",
        "answers": ["Sebastian", "Sebastian Michaelis"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) What condition does Ciel share with his mother?",
        "answers": ["Asthma"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) Which character is fond of horseback riding?",
        "answers": ["Ciel Phantomhive", "Ciel"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) When's Ciel's birthday?",
        "answers": ["December 14th, 1875"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) How tall is Sebastian?",
        "answers": ["185 cm", " 6 foot 1 inch"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) How does Sebastian appear when summoned?",
        "answers": ["A raven", "A crow"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) Which Japanese word does Sebastian's last name come from?",
        "answers": ["Mikairi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) Who was the Anicent Egyptian mummy that Sebastian met?",
        "answers": ["Smenkhkare"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) What does Sebastian claim responsibility doing five hundred years ago?",
        "answers": ["The Black Death"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) What about Sebastian is a secret according to Yana Toboso?",
        "answers": ["His age"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) What is one of Sebastian's alias",
        "answers": ["Black", "Mr. Michaelis"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) Sebastian doesn't _____.",
        "answers": ["Sleep"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) Who is Sebastian named after?",
        "answers": ["A dog", "Ciel's dog"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Black Butler) What does Sebastian help Elizabeth with in the first episode?",
        "answers": ["A ball"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) What title comes from the Portuguese word that means selection?",
        "answers": ["Selecao"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) The OP contains a line from which William Shakespeare play?",
        "answers": ["Julius Caesar"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Which character's name comes from the Portuguese word that means judge?",
        "answers": ["Juiz"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Which American radio station does the taxi driver plays in episode 1?",
        "answers": ["WPGC 95.5"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) What baseball team's hat is the taxi driver wearing in episode 1?",
        "answers": ["Washington Nationals"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) What Meg Ryan movie is referenced by Akira in episode 2?",
        "answers": ["Kate and Leopold"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Which classic movie does the big earth statue in episode three refers to?",
        "answers": ["Scarface"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Who's older) Akira or Saki?",
        "answers": ["Saki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) What is Akira's occupation?",
        "answers": ["Prince"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Which movie is the only one that Akira and his mother saw together?",
        "answers": ["Dumbo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) What character's affections does Saki not return?",
        "answers": ["Ohsuji"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Who's taller) Saki or Akira?",
        "answers": ["Akira"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Who's the leader of Eden of the East?",
        "answers": ["Kazuomi Hirasaawa", "Kazuomi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) What number Selecao is Akira?",
        "answers": ["Number 9"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) What does NEET stand for?",
        "answers": ["Not in Education, Employment, or Training"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Who is Selecao number 5?",
        "answers": ["Hajime Hiura'Hajime"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Who is known as Panties?",
        "answers": ["Yutaka Itazu", "Yutaka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Which character is really good with computers?",
        "answers": ["Mikuru Katsuhara", "Mikuru"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Who is Saki's older sister?",
        "answers": ["Asako"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Higashi no Eden) Who is Selecao number 11?",
        "answers": ["Kuroha Shiratori", "Diana Shiratori", "Diana", "Kuroha"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) Who often wastes money even when in need of it?",
        "answers": ["Yato"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What does Noragami mean?",
        "answers": ["Stray god"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What is Yato's real name?",
        "answers": ["Yaboku"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) Yukine is assumed to have died from _____ _____ _____ _____.",
        "answers": ["Abuse from his father"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What does Yukine mean?",
        "answers": ["Sound of the snow"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) Yuki means _____.",
        "answers": ["Snow"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) Who accidentally named Yaboku Yato?",
        "answers": ["Sakura"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What song is Yato's English theme song?",
        "answers": ["Don't You Forget About Me by Simple Minds"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What phobia does Yato have?",
        "answers": ["Athazagoraphobia"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What is Iki's birthday?",
        "answers": ["June 28th "]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What is Iki's character song?",
        "answers": ["Mitai Sekai"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) Which Soul Eater character does Yukine share his English voice actor with?",
        "answers": ["Soul Eater Evans", "Soul", "Soul Eater"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) Besides his true name, what is one other name that Yato goes by?",
        "answers": ["Yatty", "Jersey", "Tracksuit"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What is Yato the god of?",
        "answers": ["War", "Calamity", "Depravity", "Fortune"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What color are Yukine's eyes?",
        "answers": ["Amber"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What is Iki's race?",
        "answers": ["Human", "Half-ayakanshi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) Who are Hiyori's closest friends?",
        "answers": ["Yama and Ami"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) Which two characters sung Ai wa Yaoyorozu?",
        "answers": ["Kofuku and Daikoku"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) What is Ebisu attempting to gain control of?",
        "answers": ["Phantoms"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Noragami) Which character has a tendency to get lost?",
        "answers": ["Ebisu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) What song does Sun use to power up Nagasumi?",
        "answers": ["Song of the Heroes"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Who said) Honor among thieves is honor under the seas?",
        "answers": ["Sun Seto'Sun"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Who is the long lost sibling of Akeno Shiranui?",
        "answers": ["Masa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Masa and _ _ are the only two who accept the relationship between Nagasumi and Sun.",
        "answers": ["Sun's mother"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) What is Maki's title?",
        "answers": ["Spiral Shell", "Conch shell"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Who tries to eat Nagasumi so that the Merfolk can go home?",
        "answers": ["Shark Fujishiro", "Shark"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Who is Lunar's English voice actor?",
        "answers": ["Cherami Leigh"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Who disrupted the wedding between Lunar and Nagasumi?",
        "answers": ["Sun"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Which character's father is modeled after the Terminator?",
        "answers": ["Lunar"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Which two characters' personalities are similar?",
        "answers": ["Mawari and Sun"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Which character's human form is a parody of a character from Dragon Ball?",
        "answers": ["Saru", "Chimp", "Hideyoshi", "Hideyoshi Sarutobi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Who is a meganekko?",
        "answers": ["Class Rep"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Which phobia does Kai have?",
        "answers": ["Agoraphobia"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Who's true form is a repulsive and overweight catfish?",
        "answers": ["Yoshiuo Minamoto", "Yoshiuo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Yoshiuo is the _ _ of the anime.",
        "answers": ["Final antigonist"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Which anime is this series a carbon copy of?",
        "answers": ["Rosario+Vampire"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) What anime shares a director with this series?",
        "answers": ["Magikano"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) What is the opening theme called?",
        "answers": ["Romantic Summer by SUN&LUNAR"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Which Dragon Ball character makes a cameo in episode 18?",
        "answers": ["Goku"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Seto no Hanayome) Name one of the animes that make a character cameo in episode 16?",
        "answers": ["Dragon Ball Z", "Neon Genesis Evangelion"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) What does Linda mean in Spanish and Portuguese?",
        "answers": ["Beautiful", "Pretty"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Who is Koko's 'future husband'?",
        "answers": ["Mitsuo Yanagisawa", "Mitsuo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) What was Linda's response to Banri?",
        "answers": ["Yes"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Who is Mitsuo flirting with at the end of the anime?",
        "answers": ["Linda"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Who is Koko's boyfriend?",
        "answers": ["Banri"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Who is the fiancee of Linda's brother?",
        "answers": ["Konyakusha"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Besides Linda who else was Banri's classmate?",
        "answers": ["Abu", "Itou", "Koba", "Meiko'Nakagawa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Who lives next door to Banri?",
        "answers": ["Nana"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Who is called Miss Ultrasonic?",
        "answers": ["Oka Chinami", "Oka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Who created VJ?",
        "answers": ["Satou Takaya", "Satou"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Who are members of Tea Club?",
        "answers": ["Shii and Sao"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Linda's voice actress is _______.",
        "answers": ["Ai Kayano"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Banri's voice actor is _______.",
        "answers": ["Makoto Furukawa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Koko's voice actress is _____.",
        "answers": ["Yui Horie"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Mitsuo's voice actor is _____.",
        "answers": ["Kaito Ishikawa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) What happened in the final episode between Koko and Banri?",
        "answers": ["They got engaged"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) What episode did Koko get arrested?",
        "answers": ["Episode 7"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) What does Banri's spirit promise Banri?",
        "answers": ["To make his life a living hell"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) Why did Mitsuo enter Fukurai?",
        "answers": ["To get away from Koko"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Golden Time) How does Koko find out where Mitsuo is going to school?",
        "answers": ["Her family donated to the school", "family donation", "family donated"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) Who is the creator's favorite character?",
        "answers": ["Touko Fukawa", "Touko", "Toko"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) What's one name that Kyoko Kirigiri go by?",
        "answers": ["Ultimate Detective", "DSC number 919"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) What's Makoto Naegi's zodiac sign?",
        "answers": ["Aquarius"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) What is Monokuma afraid of?",
        "answers": ["Mice"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) One of Makoto's other names are?",
        "answers": ["Ultimate Hope", "Ultimate Lucky Student"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) What's Makoto's blood type?",
        "answers": ["A"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) Makato's chest is _____?",
        "answers": ["30 inches"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) What are Makoto's hobbies?",
        "answers": ["Watching TV and video games", "playing video games and watching tv"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) What does Makoto mean in Japanese?",
        "answers": ["Faithfulness"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) What does Naegi mean in Japanese?",
        "answers": ["Seedlings"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) What is Aoi Asahina's birthday?",
        "answers": ["April 24th "]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) Which self healing technique does Aoi practice?",
        "answers": ["Kanpu masatsu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) How many sports does Aoi play?",
        "answers": ["6 sports"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) Hina wears _____ during all seasons.",
        "answers": ["Shorts"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) Who is the main antagonist of the series?",
        "answers": ["Junko Enoshima", "Junko"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) Who is the twin sister of Junko?",
        "answers": ["Mukuro"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) When was Junko's anime debut?",
        "answers": ["Episode 12"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) Who killed Chihiro Fujisaki?",
        "answers": ["Mondo Owada", "Mondo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) What is one of the names of Chihiro's creations?",
        "answers": ["Alter Ego", "Chiaki Nanami", "Usami"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Danganronpa) Who created the software and program that was used to make Monokuma?",
        "answers": ["Chihiro"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) What's one other name that Korosensi goes by?",
        "answers": ["Octopus", "God of Death", "Guinea Pig"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Which character's hobby is researching?",
        "answers": ["Nagisa Shiota", "Nagisa", "Shiota Nagisa", "Shiota"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Math is the favorite subject of which character?",
        "answers": ["Karma Akabane", "Karma", "Akabane Karuma", "Akabane"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Who's the head of the school's Broadcasting Club?",
        "answers": ["Teppei Araki", "Araki Teppei", "Teppei", "Araki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Which character graduated from Harvard?",
        "answers": ["Gakuho Asano", "Gakuho", "Asano Gakuho", "Gakuho"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Gakushu Asano's specialty is ____ ____ ____.",
        "answers": ["Being number one"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Who has the future goal of becoming an architect?",
        "answers": ["Ryunosuke Chiba", "Chiba Ryunosuke", "Chiba", "Ryunosuke"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Eiichirou Tokumoto is the Japanese voice actor of which character?",
        "answers": ["Furyou"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) The code name This Manga is Awesome belongs to?",
        "answers": ["Yuzuki Fuwa", "Yuzuki", "Fuwa", "Fuwa Yuzuki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) The Death Roll is the signature move of which character?",
        "answers": ["Sumire", "Sumire Hara", "Hara", "Hara Sumire"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Which character's motto is Learning and killing are of one body?",
        "answers": ["Korosensei"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Who gave Nagisa the codename Gender?",
        "answers": ["Rio Nakamura", "Rio", "Nakamura", "Nakamura Rio"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Karma is depicted as ___ ____.",
        "answers": ["A devil"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Teppei is a student of which class?",
        "answers": ["3-A"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Gakuho Asano is represented by a ______.",
        "answers": ["Centipede"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Which character shares their birthday with Ritsu",
        "answers": ["Gakushu Asano", "Asano Gakushu", "Asano", "Gakushu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Ryunosuke's hobby is _____.",
        "answers": ["Triangulation"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Yuzuki's birthday is _____ _____.",
        "answers": ["February 9th"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Hara's best subject is ____ _____.",
        "answers": ["Home Economics"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) According to Aguri, Korosensei is not _______.",
        "answers": ["Japanese"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) What is Nagasi's zodiac sign?",
        "answers": ["Cancer"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Karma's most treasured item is a collection of ____ from around the world.",
        "answers": ["Spices"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) How old is Gakuho?",
        "answers": ["41 years old"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) How many languages does Gakushu know how to speak",
        "answers": ["5 languages"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Assassination Classroom) Who's in love with Nagisa?",
        "answers": ["Kaede Kayano", "Akari Yukimura", "Kayano Kaede", "Yukimura Akari", "Kaede", "Akari"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Which character's avatar is called Silver Crow?",
        "answers": ["Arita Haruyuki", "Arita", "Haruyuki Arita", "Haruyuki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) The legion Arita is in is called __________.",
        "answers": ["Nega Nebulus", "Black Legion"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) What is Arita's zodiac sign?",
        "answers": ["Taurus"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Arita's birthday is _____ _____.",
        "answers": ["April 23rd"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) What in WW2 particularly interests Arita",
        "answers": ["German vehicles", "German Tanks"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Which move is Silver Crow's special move?",
        "answers": ["Headbutt"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Who is Arita's partner?",
        "answers": ["Kuroyukihime"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Which character used to date Takumu Mayuzumi?",
        "answers": ["Chiyuri Kurashima", "Chiyuri", "Kurashima Chiyuri", "Kurashima"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) How tall is Chiyuri?",
        "answers": ["156 cm", "5 foot 11 inches"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Chiyuri's weight is ______.",
        "answers": ["51 kg", "123 Ibs"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) What's Chiyuri's avatar called?",
        "answers": ["Lime Bell"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) _____ ______ is Chiyuri's special move.",
        "answers": ["Citron Call"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) What shape is Chiyuri's pin",
        "answers": ["A cat face", "cat face"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Who is Chiyuri's Japanese voice actress?",
        "answers": ["Aki Toyosaki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Which character's name liteally means Black Snow Princess?",
        "answers": ["Kuroyukihime"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) What is Kuroyukihime's blood type?",
        "answers": ["AB"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Kuroyukihime's classification is ____ _____.",
        "answers": ["Burst Linker"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Which SAO character does Kuroyukihime share her birthday with?",
        "answers": ["Asuna Yuuki", "Asuna", "Yuuki Asuna", "Yuuki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) The name of Kuroyukihime's Burst Link Avatar is ____ _____.",
        "answers": ["Black Lotus"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) What is the name of Kuroyukihime's English voice actress?",
        "answers": ["Kira Buckland"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) How old is Kuroyukihime?",
        "answers": ["14-15 years old"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Which character has the zodiac sign Aries?",
        "answers": ["Takumu Mayuzumi", "Takumu", "Mayuzumi Takumu", "Mayuzumi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) What level is Takumu?",
        "answers": ["Level 5"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) The date of Takumu's birth is ____ _____.",
        "answers": ["April 2nd"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) How many special moves does Takumu have?",
        "answers": ["3 special moves"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Takumu's avatar's name is ____ ____",
        "answers": ["Cyan Pile"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) Which legion was Takumu originally aligned with?",
        "answers": ["Blue Legion", "Leonids"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Accel World) What does Taku call Kuroyukihime after joining the Black Legion",
        "answers": ["Master"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Which race is represented by the Queen?",
        "answers": ["Angel", "Flugel", "Heavenly Winged"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) The race that is represented by the King is ____ ____",
        "answers": ["The Imanity", "Imanity"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) What races are represented by a rook?",
        "answers": ["Elf and Lunamana"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Bishops represent which races?",
        "answers": ["Dwarf and Ex-machina"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Vampires and mermaids are represented by which piece?",
        "answers": ["Knight"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Name one race that a pawn represents.",
        "answers": ["Old Deus", "Phantasma", "Elemental", "Dragonia", "Gigant", "Fairy", "Demonia", "Werebeast"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) When you have all 16 pieces who do you face?",
        "answers": ["Tet"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Who is the first representative to bet his race's piece?",
        "answers": ["Sora"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) The relationship between Sora and Shiro is what?",
        "answers": ["Step siblings"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) In the Hebrew alphabet, Tet is the _____ ______.",
        "answers": ["9th letter"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Which game series' characters does Sora imitate in episode 3?",
        "answers": ["Ace Attorney"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) In episode 11, which Persona character is shown?",
        "answers": ["Chie Satonaka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Which pose does Sora do when asking Jibril information about the Eastern Federation",
        "answers": ["The Gendo Pose"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) When Stephanie was pounding her head on the wall in episode 11, which Jojo's Bizarre Adventure character's cry does she use?",
        "answers": ["Brando Dio"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) The Steins; Gate character _____ ______ appears in episode 11.",
        "answers": ["Makise Kurisu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) How many races have Sora and Shiro not seen",
        "answers": ["6 races"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Which races haven't been seen in the anime at all?",
        "answers": ["Gigants, Lunamana, and Fairies"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) What is another name for Flugel",
        "answers": ["Angel", "Heavenly Winged"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Another name for Dhampir is ____.",
        "answers": ["Vampire"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Werebeast has another name the race goes by, what is it?",
        "answers": ["Warbeast"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) The official name of mermaids is what?",
        "answers": ["Seiren"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) What word does Sora and Shiro's names, when written in Japanese, put together make?",
        "answers": ["Blank"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) What is the tenth pledge?",
        "answers": ["Let's all have fun and play together", "have fun and play together", "play together and have fun"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) In games, what does each player bet?",
        "answers": ["Something they agree is equal value", "equal value"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) What does Shiro mean in Japanese?",
        "answers": ["White"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) In a Charapedia poll, which character got ranked 5th smartest anime character?",
        "answers": ["Sora"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Which character's name is an Arabic reading of Gabriel?",
        "answers": ["Jibril"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) The Japanese voice actor for this character is Yoko Hikasa. Who is it?",
        "answers": ["Stephanie Dota", "Stephanie"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Which race is 3rd?",
        "answers": ["Elemental"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(No Game No Life) Lunamanas have which rank?",
        "answers": ["13th rank"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Which character is the only miko?",
        "answers": ["Akira Amatsume", "Akira", "Amatsume Akira", "Amatsume"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) In the anime, Akira was the first to share what with her love interest?",
        "answers": ["A bath"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Akira is the only character to have what?",
        "answers": ["A cat"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Who is Akira's half sister?",
        "answers": ["Kazuha"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Where does Akira live?",
        "answers": ["In a sacred Shinto shrine", "sacred shinto shrine"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Akira is the ____ _____ out of the heroines.",
        "answers": ["2nd smallest"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Who's the first character to get molested?",
        "answers": ["Haruka Kasugano"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) How many girls like Haruka?",
        "answers": ["7 girls"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) How does Haruka cope with the lost of his and Sora's parents?",
        "answers": ["A stout heart", "stout heart"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Haru is the first character to commit what",
        "answers": ["Incestuous actions"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) When is Sora and Haru's birthday?",
        "answers": ["February 5th"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) The Kasugano twins' zodiac sign is what?",
        "answers": ["Aquarius"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) What is Sora Kasugano almost never seen without?",
        "answers": ["Her stuffed rabbit", "stuffed rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) What does Sora have an irrational fear of?",
        "answers": ["Mosquitoes"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Who was the only character to attempt suicide?",
        "answers": ["Sora"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Sora is the only ___ ____ character in the anime,",
        "answers": ["Anti-social"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Who does Sora marry?",
        "answers": ["Her brother", "Haruka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) How tall is Sora?",
        "answers": ["152 cm", "4 foot 9 inches"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Which character is the only ojou-sama of the series?",
        "answers": ["Kazuha Migiwa", "Kazuha", "Migiwa Kazuha", "Migiwa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Out of her friends, which one does Kazuha like the least?",
        "answers": ["Ryouhei Nakazato", "Ryouhei", "Nakazato Ryouhei", "Nakazato"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Who is one of Kazuha's employees?",
        "answers": ["Motoka Nogisaka", "Motoka", "Nogisaka Motoka", "Nogisaka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Kazuha's father is an _____ ______.",
        "answers": ["Influential magnate"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) What color is Kazuha's swimsuit?",
        "answers": ["Blue with white polka dots"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) The Japanese voice actress for Kazuha in the anime is who?",
        "answers": ["Ryoko Ono"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Who's zodiac sign is Libra?",
        "answers": ["Nao Yorihime", "Yorihime Nao", "Nao", "Yorihime"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Nao is the one of the only characters that suffers from ______.",
        "answers": ["Tension"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) What does Nao's name mean in Japanese?",
        "answers": ["Honest"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) Nao is the most ______ of the heroines.",
        "answers": ["Adult like"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) When is Nao's birthday?",
        "answers": ["October 7th"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Yosuga no Sora) How old is Nao?",
        "answers": ["17 years old"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Name one car in the anime that Shuichi Shigeno owned.",
        "answers": ["Toyota Trueno AE86", "Subaru WRX"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Who is the original inspiration of the driver of the Eight-Six?",
        "answers": ["Dorikin", "Dori-Dori", "Keiichi Tsuchiya", "Keiichi", "Tsuchiya"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) What color does the sportsbike rider who appears in the 3rd stage and overtook Takumi wear?",
        "answers": ["Green"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) The Akina Speedstars and Seven Star Leaves are named after which wheel brand?",
        "answers": ["Speed Star Racing"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) In Japanese, the name Takumi means what?",
        "answers": ["Skillful", "Clever"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) One Hong Kong superstar that were previously attached to the live action movie is _____ ____.",
        "answers": ["Jackie Chan", "Andy Lau", "Tsui Hark"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Which variant of Eurodisco owes its decent popularity to this series?",
        "answers": ["Eurobeat"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) The anime _____ _____ also features a character name Takumi Fujiwara.",
        "answers": ["Dear Boys"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) TP was intending to market the series as what for a new generation.",
        "answers": ["Speed Racer"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) The Toyota Trueno was made in ____ _____ _____.",
        "answers": ["The year 1983"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) What does Bunta own besides a car?",
        "answers": ["A tofu shop"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) _____ _____ plays Takumi in the live action movie.",
        "answers": ["Jay Chou"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) This series got the ______ _______ spot in Watch Mojo's Top 10 best anime soundtracks.",
        "answers": ["Number 1"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Name one thing that Takumi dislikes.",
        "answers": ["Showoffs", "Losing", "Girls that flirt"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) The Toyota Corolla Levin SR (AE85) belongs to which character?",
        "answers": ["Itsuki Takeuchi", "Itsuki", "Takeuchi Itsuki", "Takeuchi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Hiroshi Fumihiro's Madza is which character?",
        "answers": ["Classic red"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Which character is the leader of the Speedstars?",
        "answers": ["Kouichirou Iketani", "Kouichirou", "Iketani Kouichirou", "Iketani"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) This character shares a name with a character in Scooby Doo and the Samurai Sword. Who is it?",
        "answers": ["Kenji"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Natsuki Mogi's Japanese voice actress in the main series is who?",
        "answers": ["Ayako Kawasumi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) What car does Kenta Nakamura own?",
        "answers": ["Nissan Silvia Q's Aero (S14)"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) The Black Lightning is an alias for which character?",
        "answers": ["Takeshi Nakazato", "Takeshi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) In the Tokyopop dub, who voices Saori?",
        "answers": ["Colleen O'Shaughnessey"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) A __________ kept Iketani and Mako apart.",
        "answers": ["Misunderstanding"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Who is Mako's navigator?",
        "answers": ["Sayuki", "Simone"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) How does Shingo Shoji drive?",
        "answers": ["Dangerously"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Which character drives a Toyota Chaser?",
        "answers": ["Yuuichi Tachibana'Tachibana Yuuichi", "Tachibana", "Yuuichi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) The car that Ryousuke drives is what?",
        "answers": ["A 1990 Mazda Savanna RX-7"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) What kind of drive does Keisuke Takahashi dislike?",
        "answers": ["Four wheel drive", "4WD"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Who is Takumi's Korean voice actor?",
        "answers": ["Jun Seok Song"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Bunta in Japanese means ________.",
        "answers": ["Sentence", "Writing", "Design"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) _______ _______ is what Fumihiro's name in Japanese means.",
        "answers": ["Wide sentence"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Kouichirou is how tall?",
        "answers": ["175 cm", "5 foot 7 inches"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) In Japanese, Kenji means _____ _____ _____.",
        "answers": ["Twice as wise"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) The meaning of Natsuki's name in Japanese is what?",
        "answers": ["Summer", "Hope"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Kenta means ______ in Japanese.",
        "answers": ["Healthy", "Strong", "Thick", "Big"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) What does Takeshi in Japanese mean?",
        "answers": ["Warrior", "Fierce"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) One meaning of Saori's name is what?",
        "answers": ["Sun child", "Bright sun"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Mako's name means _____ _____ ______ in Japanese.",
        "answers": ["Child of truth"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Sayuki's Spanish voice actress is ______ ______.",
        "answers": ["Mireya Mendoza"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) My _______ is what Shingo means in Japanese.",
        "answers": ["Humility"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) In Japanese Yuuichi means what?",
        "answers": ["Kind one"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Which character's name means good help in Japanese?",
        "answers": ["Ryousuke"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Keisuke's name means what in Japanese?",
        "answers": ["Save"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) What kind of trees does Itsuki's name mean in Japanese?",
        "answers": ["Timber trees"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Who is Itsuki's Brazilian voice actor?",
        "answers": ["Yuri Chesman"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Fabrizio Manfredi is which character's Italian voice actor?",
        "answers": ["Keisuke"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Which character shares a voice actor with Axel from the Kingdom Hearts series and Reno from the Final Fantasy series?",
        "answers": ["Shingo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) What car does Natsuki's sugar daddy drive?",
        "answers": ["A white Mercedes", "A Mercedes"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) Takeshi is the leader of _____ _____ ______.",
        "answers": ["The Myogi Nightkids", "Myogi Nightkids"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Initial D) What color is Takumi's car?",
        "answers": ["High tech two tone"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) What tokusatsu series is the alien that Yuko tries to befriend in episode 10 from?",
        "answers": ["Ultraman"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Which gaming system is Sasahara seen playing in episode 2?",
        "answers": ["Virtual Boy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) In episode 12, the gun that Misato uses to shoot at Sasahara is what model?",
        "answers": ["P90 Submachine Gun"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) The blackbird in episode 26 is based on what?",
        "answers": ["An airship", "An American airship", "A reconnaissance aircraft"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) What is the video game based on the series called?",
        "answers": ["Nichijou) Uchuujin", "Regular Life) Alien"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) The system that the video game is on is what?",
        "answers": ["PSP", "Playstation Portable"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Who said) Super Ultra Great Delicious Wonderful Bad?",
        "answers": ["Yuuko Aioi", "Aioi Yuuko", "Aioi", "Yuuko"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) How many pets does Mai Minakami have?",
        "answers": ["3 pets"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Why does Mio Naganohara goes on a rampage in episode 5?",
        "answers": ["The teacher was impressed with Yuuko's drawing"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Sakamoto has how many character songs?",
        "answers": ["5 character songs"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) When is Nano Shinonome's birthday?",
        "answers": ["August 7th "]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) What is Hakase's English name?",
        "answers": ["Professor"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) The subject Akagi teaches at Tokisadame High School is what?",
        "answers": ["Math"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Which Lucky Star character bears a resemblance to Haruna Annaka?",
        "answers": ["Tsukasa Hiiragi", "Tsukasa", "Hiiragi Tsukasa", "Hiiragi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) _____ _____ _____ is the character Etsuko Kozakura voices.",
        "answers": ["Biscuit No. 2"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) What does Karasu need in order to talk?",
        "answers": ["Sakamoto's scarf"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Kenzaburou Daiku is the president of which club?",
        "answers": ["Igo soccer"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) How does Fey die?",
        "answers": ["Trips over his feet"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) The occupation that Masaharu Egi has is what?",
        "answers": ["Flowing noodle researcher"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Name one of Fecchan's friends.",
        "answers": ["Misato", "Weboshi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) _________'s grandfather is the gentleman.",
        "answers": ["Kiyoshi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Who's the vice principal's daughter?",
        "answers": ["Kimiko"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) What is unknown to most about Principal Shinonome?",
        "answers": ["He's a talented wrestler"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Which character has a crush on Izumi Sakurai?",
        "answers": ["Manabu Takasaki", "Takasaki", "Manabu", "Takasaki Manabu"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Manabu's last name is a reference to a city. Which region is it in?",
        "answers": ["Gunma"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) _______ is the character Kana Nakamura is always trying to capture.",
        "answers": ["Nano"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Yuria Sekiguchi is interested in what?",
        "answers": ["Calligraphy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) At some point what was Matoko Sakurai's occupation?'The daifuku mascot",
        "answers": ["Daifuku mascot"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) What is Tanaka's afro used for?",
        "answers": ["To store stuff"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Who is often the victim of Nakamura's failed attempts to catch Nano?",
        "answers": ["Nakanojo Tsuyoshi", "Nakanojo", "Tsuyoshi Nakanojou", "Tsuyoshi"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Ogi is the only one who knows the rules to what?",
        "answers": ["Igo soccer"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Why does Koujirou Sasahara wear glasses?",
        "answers": ["For show"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Which attitude does Misato Tachibana have?",
        "answers": ["Tsundere"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) The character that likes rock music is who?",
        "answers": ["Weboshii"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Name one of Yoshino Naganohara's abilities?",
        "answers": ["Kendo", "Prankster", "Expert prankster", "Cooking"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) ________ _______  is Mihoshi Tachibana's voice actress.",
        "answers": ["Manami Honda"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Where does Tamamura work?",
        "answers": ["Daiku cafe", "At a cafe", "A cafe"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Who is Dolph's enemy?",
        "answers": ["Princess Starla"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Which character is implied as Sumika's sibling?",
        "answers": ["Kenzaburou"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Tanabo mistakes Yuuko as who?",
        "answers": ["Double Cheeseburgirl"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) One of the books that Hajime Sakurai has written is ______",
        "answers": ["Steam", "Milk Snow", "Relay Cropping"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Mi-chan is very good at throwing what?",
        "answers": ["Baseballs"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Tsuyoshi's father owns a _____ ______",
        "answers": ["Daifuku stand"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) The mysterious dog who comforts Yuuko after an unfortunate event is named?",
        "answers": ["Buddy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) What color is Oguri Cap?",
        "answers": ["Brown and white"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) The color of Pyon's fur is what?",
        "answers": ["White"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) What is Mio often seen reading?",
        "answers": ["The newspaper", "Newspaper"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) This series' video game is the premise of what?",
        "answers": ["Yuuko's classroom dreams"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) What does Mai write?",
        "answers": ["Music"]
    },
    {
        "question": "(Nichijou) Why didn't Hakase like Mai at first?",
        "answers": ["Mai's dogs"]
    },
  {
    "question": "(Whisper of the Heart) Which company created the clock in the antique shop? ",
    "answers": ["Porco Rosso"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Rurouni Kenshin) What type of sword does Kenshin use, where the leading edge is dull, and the back side is the cutting edge?",
    "answers": ["sakabatou"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Gunsmith Cats) What unusual item do Rally and Minnie May keep in their refrigerator?",
    "answers": ["Plastic explosives"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Gunsmith Cats) What is Rally's ethnicity?",
    "answers": ["East Indian/Japanese"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Gunsmith Cats) What is Rally's favorite handgun?",
    "answers": ["Czech CZ75", "A Czech CZ75"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Gunbuster Aim for the Top!) What was given to Amano prior to leaving on her final mission?",
    "answers": ["origami", "origami tsuru"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Grave of the Fireflies) What candy does Setsuko carry? ",
    "answers": ["Morinaga Drops"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fruits Basket) How does Kyo enter the Sohma residence the first time we meet him?",
    "answers": ["the roof"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fruits Basket) What does Shigure add to his curry that Yuki doesn't think belongs?",
    "answers": ["Takuan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fruits Basket) What size apartment does Uo-chan live in?",
    "answers": ["1DK"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Chobits) What is Yumi's Breast size?",
    "answers": ["E-cup"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Card Captor Sakura) In episode 11, what is the 'very precious thing' that Tomoyo had in the box that was sealed by the shield card?",
    "answers": ["An eraser"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Card Captor Sakura) When did Sakura and Tomoyo first meet?",
    "answers": ["3rd grade", "Third grade"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bubblegum Crisis) In 'Double Vision,' Who manufactured the portable computer that Daley is using to pull up information?",
    "answers": ["Toshiba"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bubblegum Crisis) In 'Double Vision,' What type of car does Sylia drive?",
    "answers": ["Mercedes C-III"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bubblegum Crisis) What company makes Priss' motorcycle?",
    "answers": ["Genom"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bubblegum Crisis) What language was the code written in on Sylia's data cartridge from her father?",
    "answers": ["BASIC"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bubblegum Crisis) What 1982 movie influenced Priss' name and the name of her rock band?",
    "answers": ["Blade Runner"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Lupin III) Which TV station was Fujiko working for when they were televising the wedding?",
    "answers": ["NBK"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Love Hina) In the Winter Special of Love Hina, we see Kitsune and Shinobu try to get money by selling manga, one of Akamatsu-sensei's old works. What series are they selling?",
    "answers": ["Ai Ga Tomaranai"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The pilots in Macross Plus were testing two new veritechs, the YF-19 and the YF-21. These names are based on US military convention. What do the letters represent?",
    "answers": ["Prototype &amp; Fighter"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Macross universe references products of a well known computer company. What does Macross sound like?",
    "answers": ["Mac OS"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Oh! My Goddess!) What sort of motorcycle does Keiichi ride?",
    "answers": ["BMW Boxer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Oh! My Goddess!) In episode 5, what does Skuld use for energy food?",
    "answers": ["Ice cream"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Oh! My Goddess!) What pizza company was Keichi working for in Episode 5?",
    "answers": ["Domino's"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Oh! My Goddess!) In episode 5, what brand computer does Skuld use to do the calculations for the Ultimate Magic Circle?",
    "answers": ["NIC PC"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In episode 3, on the back of Keichi's jacket, there's a homophonic version of his name. What is it?",
    "answers": ["K-1"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Project A-ko) Captain Napolipolita is a parody of what well-known anime character?",
    "answers": ["Captain Harlock"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Project A-ko) Who are Magami Eiko's (A-ko) parents?",
    "answers": ["Clark Kent &amp; Diana Prince"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Patlabor) To operate the labor, what password does Noa enter into the console?",
    "answers": ["Alphonse"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Patlabor) In the second movie, what are the words used to disable Tsuge's computer-controlled blimps quoting?",
    "answers": ["Gospel of Luke"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Neon Genesis Evangelion) In episode 23, a word is spray-painted at the back of Rei's underground room. What is the word?",
    "answers": ["strangeness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Neon Genesis Evangelion) In episode 15, there is a key scene in which Rei is inside an overgrown test-tube. What do the surrounding letters represent?",
    "answers": ["nucleotides"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Neon Genesis Evangelion) Which well-known company did Asuka use to move her personal belongings into Misato's apartment?",
    "answers": ["DHL"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Neon Genesis Evangelion) What character is Misato based on?",
    "answers": ["Fujiko Mine", "Mine Fujiko"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Neon Genesis Evangelion) What saying is printed across the bottom of the NERV crest?",
    "answers": ["God's In His Heaven. All's Right With The World."]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's reported that Shoujo Kakumei Utena was heavily influenced by another anime/manga series. Which one?",
    "answers": ["Versailles no Bara", "Rose of Versailles"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Speed Racer) The main character's Japanese name, Mifune Go, is named after a real person? Who?",
    "answers": ["Toshiro Mifune", "Mifune Toshiro"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Video Girl Ai) What is Moteuchi Yota's nickname?",
    "answers": ["Motenai Moteuichi"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When Lain gets her new Navi, what is the operating system that it's running?",
    "answers": ["Copeland"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The characters of Log Horizon are trapped in what game?",
    "answers": ["Elder Tale"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the fourth heroine in The World Only God Knows?",
    "answers": ["Shiori Shiomiya", "Shiomiya Shiori"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who voiced Konata in Lucky☆Star?",
    "answers": ["Hirano Aya", "Aya Hirano"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who published 東方靈異伝　～ The Highly Responsive to Prayers?",
    "answers": ["Amusement Makers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who created Lucky☆Star?",
    "answers": ["Yoshimizu Kagami"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Besides VHS, in what medium was Neon Genesis Evangelion's first home release?",
    "answers": ["Laserdisc"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Moriya Shrine's original goddess?",
    "answers": ["Moriya Suwako", "Suwako Moriya"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the first person killed by Yagami Light?",
    "answers": ["Otoharada Kurou", "Kurou Otoharada"]
  },
  {
    "question": "﻿Which genre is aimed at girls between 10-18?",
    "answers": [
      "shoujo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When was the first known Japanese animation produced?",
    "answers": [
      "1917"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The practice of dressing up like anime characters in Japan is called?",
    "answers": [
      "cosplay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In yaoi pairing, what is the \"receiving\", \"bottom\", or passive partner known as?",
    "answers": [
      "uke"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In yaoi pairing, what is the \"top\" or dominant partner known as?",
    "answers": [
      "seme"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a popular anime/manga character archetype that derives from the Japanese pronunciation of the English word 'cool'?",
    "answers": [
      "kuudere",
      "coodere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a Japanese term for a character development process that describes a person who is initially cold and even hostile towards another person before gradually showing their warm side over time?",
    "answers": [
      "tsundere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Type of anime aimed at young boys under the age of fifteen?",
    "answers": [
      "shonen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Type of anime aimed at young men between the ages of 15-24?",
    "answers": [
      "seinen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Type of anime aimed at adult women?",
    "answers": [
      "josei"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Type of anime largely focused on one distinct aspect: pilotable robots?",
    "answers": [
      "mecha",
      "robot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Type of anime about innocent young girls using a magical object to transform into a superhero version of themselves?",
    "answers": [
      "magical girl",
      "mahou shoujo",
      "majokko"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Type of anime which do not show sexual intercourse or genitalia, but sexual themes are referenced?",
    "answers": [
      "ecchi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Type of anime where one male character, the protagonist, at the center of a group of female characters who are all vying for his romantic affections?",
    "answers": [
      "harem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What character type is a heroine that started as a villain trying to kill the protagonist but then switched to his side after falling in love with him?",
    "answers": [
      "mayadere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's common in anime for a character to pull their lower eyelid down to taunt someone. What is this called?",
    "answers": [
      "akanabe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What anime character type is known as a quiet and often antisocial character?",
    "answers": [
      "dandere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What character type is very loving and gentle to someone before their devotion becomes destructive in nature, often through violence and/or brutality?",
    "answers": [
      "yandere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Hayao Miyazaki movie was based off of a book by a British author named Dianna Wynne Jones?",
    "answers": [
      "Castle in the sky"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2015, among all the 17 long anime movies Hayao Miyazaki participated in, how many did he direct?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "eleven"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) Who is the main character?",
    "answers": [
      "Eren Yeager",
      "Eren"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) Which character loves to eat?",
    "answers": [
      "Sasha Blouse",
      "Sasha"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) What is the outer wall named (The one taken by the titans)?",
    "answers": [
      "Wall Maria",
      "Maria"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) How many men did Eren kill during the scene in which he rescued the kidnapped Misaka when they were children (Shingeki no Kyojin)?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "two"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) What color flare is used when the mission is over whether or nor it was a success?",
    "answers": [
      "Yellow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) Who killed Rod Reiss?",
    "answers": [
      "Historia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) What was the name of Levi's mother?",
    "answers": [
      "Kuchel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) Who taught Annie how to fight?",
    "answers": [
      "Her father",
      "Father"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) What was the name of Historia's mother?",
    "answers": [
      "Alma"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) What protects the Colossal titan?",
    "answers": [
      "Steam"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) What is the name of the wall in Wall Sina's northern district?",
    "answers": [
      "Orvud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) What is the name of the newspaper in the Stohess district?",
    "answers": [
      "Berg Newspaper",
      "Berg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) Who did Grisha eat in order to steal the Coordinate?",
    "answers": [
      "Frieda Reiss",
      "Frieda"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) Who ruined Eren's equipment when they were trainees?",
    "answers": [
      "Keith Shadis",
      "Keith",
      "Shadis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) \"Only the victors are allowed to live. This world is merciless like that.\" Who said this?",
    "answers": [
      "Mikasa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) What did Carla do for a living before she met Grisha?",
    "answers": [
      "waitress"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) \"I just don't want those charred bones I saw to be disappointed in me. I... I know what I have to do now.\" Who said this?",
    "answers": [
      "Jean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Attack on Titan) Who would become the commander of the Scouting Legion if something were to happen to Erwin?",
    "answers": [
      "Hange"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Beyblade) What is the name of Emily's bitbeast?",
    "answers": [
      "Trygator"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "English name of Kuroshitsuji?",
    "answers": [
      "Black Butler"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Black Butler) Who is the British monarch in Black Butler's time period?",
    "answers": [
      "Victoria I",
      "Queen Victoria I"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Black Cat) How many members of Chronos were there originally?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "thirteen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Black Cat) Out of which material are Train Heartnet's gun and bullets mainly made of?",
    "answers": [
      "orichalcum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Black Cat) Who is the main character?",
    "answers": [
      "Train Heartnet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which series features a location called the Soul Society?",
    "answers": [
      "Bleach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bleach) How many times have Ichigo and Renji battled?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "two"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bleach) What squad is Toushiro Hitsugaya the captain of?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "10th",
      "tenth",
      "ten"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bleach) Human mediums, having the ability to detect the existence of Hollows?",
    "answers": [
      "Quincy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bleach) What is a Hollow that has removed its mask and has gained Shinigami-like powers?",
    "answers": [
      "Arrancar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bleach) What is the name of Hitsugaya Toshirou's Zanpakutou?",
    "answers": [
      "Hyourinmaru"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bleach) Who does Orikasa Fumiko voice?",
    "answers": [
      "Rukia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what CLAMP Animé is there a little Persocon named Chii?",
    "answers": [
      "Chobits"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Chobits) What is the first thing that came on the screen in episode 1?",
    "answers": [
      "cow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Code Geass) The character Li Xingke is a member of which group?",
    "answers": [
      "the chinese federation",
      "chinese federation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Code Geass) The leader of the Four Holy Swords is named...?",
    "answers": [
      "General Kyoshiro Tohdoh",
      "general tohdoh",
      "kyoshiro tohdoh",
      "tohdoh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Code Geass) What was the white Knightmare Frame piloted by Suzaku called?",
    "answers": [
      "Lancelot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Code Geass) What game does Lelouch skip school to play?",
    "answers": [
      "chess"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Code Geass) Wat was the name of the academy Lelouch went to?",
    "answers": [
      "Ashford Academy",
      "Ashford"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Code Geass) At the very end, how many characters were aware of Lelouch's true intentions?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "four"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Cowboy Bebop) What is the villan Vicious's weapon of choice?",
    "answers": [
      "katana"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Cowboy Bebop) Who dies?",
    "answers": [
      "Spike"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime involves a Corgi hound named Ein as one of the characters?",
    "answers": [
      "cowboy bebop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) Who is the second Kira?",
    "answers": [
      "Misa Amane",
      "misa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) Who is the first Kira?",
    "answers": [
      "Light Yagami",
      "Light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) Who is the third Kira?",
    "answers": [
      "Kyosuke Higuchi",
      "Kyosuke"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) What is the default way the Death Note kills?",
    "answers": [
      "cardiac paralysis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) What is the name of the Shinigami that owns the Death Note Light Yagami uses?",
    "answers": [
      "Ryuk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) What is L's real name?",
    "answers": [
      "L Lawliet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) Who did the first Death Note to be picked up belong to?",
    "answers": [
      "Sidoh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) When Misa meets Light, what is her occupation?",
    "answers": [
      "Model"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) What nickname is given to Raito (Light) after he finds the Death Note?",
    "answers": [
      "Kira"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) What is Ryuuku's favorite food?",
    "answers": [
      "Apple"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) What did L tell the Japanese Task Force to call him?",
    "answers": [
      "Ryuzaki"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) Who was L's butler/caregiver/handler?",
    "answers": [
      "Watari"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) Who did L always call an idiot?",
    "answers": [
      "Matsuda"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) What is Light's last name?",
    "answers": [
      "Yagami"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Death Note) What was the name of the inside man in the Yotsuba group?",
    "answers": [
      "Renji Namikawa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Detective Conan) What is Shinichi Kudo's best sport?",
    "answers": [
      "soccer",
      "football"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Digimon) Which year was the American adaptation of Digimon: The Movie released?",
    "answers": [
      "2000"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Digimon) What was Taichi Kamiya's first Digimon?",
    "answers": [
      "Botamon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) How many dragon balls are there?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "seven"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) Who does a complete set of dragon balls summon?",
    "answers": [
      "Shenron"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) What race is Piccolo?",
    "answers": [
      "Namekian",
      "Nameks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) Who kills Frieza?",
    "answers": [
      "Future Trunks",
      "Trunks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) Who sacrifices his life for Gohan from an incoming blast from Nappa in the Saiyan Saga?",
    "answers": [
      "Piccolo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Dragon Ball Z) Which android is the only one who marries?",
    "answers": [
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "For which anime were these songs written: \"Cha La Head Cha La\" and \"Boku-tachi wa Tenshi Datta\"?",
    "answers": [
      "Dragon Ball Z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Durarara) What is the name of the hot tempered bar tender with super human strength?",
    "answers": [
      "Shizuo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fairy Tail) Where did Lucy get her guild mark?",
    "answers": [
      "Right hand",
      "back of right hand",
      "hand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fairy Tail) Who was the first guild master of Fairy Tail?",
    "answers": [
      "Mavis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fairy Tail) Where is the location of the Fairy Tail guildhouse?",
    "answers": [
      "Magnolia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fairy Tail) What is the name of the dragon that raised Natsu in Fairy Tail?",
    "answers": [
      "Igneel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fooly Cooly) How many manga-like (comic-like) scenes are there in total?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "two"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fooly Cooly) There are a couple of scenes where you see the commander getting a haircut. What popular show's animation resembles the special animation in this scene?",
    "answers": [
      "South Park"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fruits Basket) What is the last name of the cursed family Tohru stays with?",
    "answers": [
      "Sohma"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fruits Basket) What is the kind of animal does Momiji turn into?",
    "answers": [
      "rabbit",
      "bunny"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fruits Basket) What spirit is Akito possessed by?",
    "answers": [
      "God"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fruits Basket) What Zodiac animal is Kyo Sohma?",
    "answers": [
      "cat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What is Edward's and Alphonse's last name?",
    "answers": [
      "Elric"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Who kills Hughes?",
    "answers": [
      "Envy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What is the automotive armored prostheses?",
    "answers": [
      "automail"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What did Ed sacrifice in order to seal his brother's soul into a suit of armour?",
    "answers": [
      "right arm",
      "arm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Colonel Roy Mustang is also known as the Alchemist of__?",
    "answers": [
      "Flame"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What is King Bradley aka Pride's son called?",
    "answers": [
      "Selim"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Who taught the Elric brothers alchemy?",
    "answers": [
      "Izumi Curtis",
      "Izumi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Which Homunculus uses carbon as their power?",
    "answers": [
      "Greed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Solf J. Kimblee is known as the ___ Alchemist?",
    "answers": [
      "Crimson"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What Language is Riza's Tattoo Writen In?",
    "answers": [
      "Latin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) The Father of the Homunculi can stop which style of alchemy?",
    "answers": [
      "Western Armestris"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) In the manga what is the date in Ed's pocket watch?",
    "answers": [
      "3.Oct.10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What does Edward hate to drink?",
    "answers": [
      "milk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Basque Grand is known as the __ Alchemist?",
    "answers": [
      "Iron Blood"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) what is the first law of alchemy?",
    "answers": [
      "equivalent exchange"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Who Says This “I have no desire to live a carefree, happy life alone...\"?",
    "answers": [
      "Riza"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What room number is the Fuhrer's?",
    "answers": [
      "103"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What is Envy's nickname for Edward?",
    "answers": [
      "Fullmetal pipsqueak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What is the symbol on the back of Edward's red coat called?",
    "answers": [
      "flammel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) According To Fuhrer Bradley What Is Roy's Weakness?",
    "answers": [
      "Riza",
      "Riza Hawkeye"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) When Mustang was forced to do human transmutation in fma: brotherhood what did he loose?",
    "answers": [
      "eyesight",
      "vision"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) How is Envy related to Ed and Al?",
    "answers": [
      "brother",
      "brothers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) How tall is Edward?",
    "answers": [
      "4'6\"",
      "four and a half feet",
      "four foot six inches",
      "four foot 6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What does Winry do for a living?",
    "answers": [
      "mechanic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What's Hughes's daughter's name?",
    "answers": [
      "elicia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What is the name of Ed and Al's mother?",
    "answers": [
      "Trisha"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What did Ed give up to revive his mother?",
    "answers": [
      "left leg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Who is Ed's father?",
    "answers": [
      "Hohenheim"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) How old was Edward when he became a state alchemist?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "twelve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What is the name of the Ishbalan people's god?",
    "answers": [
      "Ishbala"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What is Winry's last name?",
    "answers": [
      "Rockbell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) What is the name of transmutation circle used to make the Philosopher Stone?",
    "answers": [
      "Grand Arcanum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Shou Tucker was known as the __ Alchemist?",
    "answers": [
      "Sewing Life"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Who kills Lust?",
    "answers": [
      "Colonel Mustang",
      "Mustang",
      "Roy mustang"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Whose nickname is the \"Ultimate Spear\"?",
    "answers": [
      "Lust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Who sparked the Ishval Civil War?",
    "answers": [
      "Envy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Who was the second Homunculus created by Father?",
    "answers": [
      "Lust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Who is the only female Homunculus?",
    "answers": [
      "Lust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Alex Louis Armstrong is also known as the __ Alchemist?",
    "answers": [
      "Strong Arm",
      "strongarm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Who is known as the Northern Wall of Briggs?",
    "answers": [
      "Olivier Mira Armstrong",
      "Olivier Armstrong"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fullmetal Alchemist) Who is a pseudo Gate of Truth?",
    "answers": [
      "Gluttony"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After Watase Yuu's creation of \"Fushigi Yuugi\", which famous shoujo anime did she make?",
    "answers": [
      "Ayashi no Ceres"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fushigi Yuugi) Miaka is the priestess of what?",
    "answers": [
      "Suzaku"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Fushigi Yuugi) The world of Fushigi Yuugi is based on the ancient form of what country?",
    "answers": [
      "China"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Gundam) How many rounds of ammunition does Gundam Wing Zero Custom's Buster Rifle have?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "three"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Gundam) What is the original Gundam?",
    "answers": [
      "RX-78"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Gundam) What is the name of the final Gundam used by Shiro in 08th MS Team?",
    "answers": [
      "Ez-8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Hellsing) What country does it take place in?",
    "answers": [
      "England"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Hetalia) Who did America grow up with?",
    "answers": [
      "England"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Hetalia) Who does Holy Rome have a crush on?",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Highschool Of The Dead) What are zombie's sensitive to?",
    "answers": [
      "sound"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(InuYasha) Who was the demon of hair?",
    "answers": [
      "Yura"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(InuYasha) Who is the leader of the wolf demons?",
    "answers": [
      "Koga",
      "kouga"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(InuYasha) InuYasha is half __ demon?",
    "answers": [
      "dog"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Inuyasha) What is the name of Sango's demon cat?",
    "answers": [
      "kirara"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(InuYasha) Inuyasha's sword is called what?",
    "answers": [
      "Tessaiga",
      "Tetsusaiga"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(InuYasha) What is the name of the baby that Naraku holds his human heart in?",
    "answers": [
      "Hakudoshi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(InuYasha) Who does Inuyasha mistake Kagome for?",
    "answers": [
      "Kikyo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Basketball Anime that came out in 2012?",
    "answers": [
      "Kuroko No Basket"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Love Hina) What was the samurai girl's name?",
    "answers": [
      "Aoyama ",
      "Aoyama Motoko"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Love Hina) In the Christmas special, what did Keitarou buy Naru?",
    "answers": [
      "Coat",
      "jacket"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Magic Knight Rayearth) Thee three heroines, Hikaru, Umi and Fuu, have powers associated with different elements. What kind of elemental spells does Umi use?",
    "answers": [
      "water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Mew Mew Power) What type of animal power does Kiki have?",
    "answers": [
      "monkey"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which 2011 magical girl anime features Grief Seeds, witches, a mysterious white creature called Kyubey, and the characters Homura, Sayaka and Mami?",
    "answers": [
      "Puella Magi Madoka Magica"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) What is the relationship between Hinata and Hanabi Hyuga?",
    "answers": [
      "sisters",
      "sister"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) Who is Negi's cousin?",
    "answers": [
      "Hinata Hyuga",
      "Hinata"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sakura, Sasuke, Rock Lee, and Kakashi are all characters from which anime?",
    "answers": [
      "Naruto"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) What is the name of Naruto's son?",
    "answers": [
      "Boruto Uzumaki",
      "Boruto"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) What is the special Kekkei Genkai/Bloodline Limit of the Hyuga clan?",
    "answers": [
      "Byakugan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) Which jutsu does Rock Lee use?",
    "answers": [
      "taijutsu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) Who tricked Naruto into stealing a sacred scroll?",
    "answers": [
      "Mizuki"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) Naruto first shows his nine-tails chakra when he fights who?",
    "answers": [
      "Haku"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) What animal does the one-tailed beast resemble?",
    "answers": [
      "Tanuki",
      "Japanese Raccoon Dog",
      "Raccoon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) What is the name of the nine-tailed beast?",
    "answers": [
      "Kurama"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) Who gave Kakashi his Sharingan eye?",
    "answers": [
      "Obito Uchiha",
      "Obito"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) Who cut Sakura's hair off?",
    "answers": [
      "Sakura"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) Name one of Sarutobi's disciples?",
    "answers": [
      "Orochimaru",
      "Jiraiya",
      "Tsunade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) What is the forbidden technique used by Rock Lee that he used on Dosu and Gaara?",
    "answers": [
      "Primary Lotus"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) D-rank missions are usually given to what level of shinobi?",
    "answers": [
      "Genin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) All members of what group are S-rank criminals?",
    "answers": [
      "Akatsuki"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) What is the word for a female ninja?",
    "answers": [
      "Kunoichi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) The Sharingan is what type of jutsu?",
    "answers": [
      "Doujutsu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) What is Naruto's favorite food?",
    "answers": [
      "Ramen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) When in The Forest Of Death, Orochimaru disguises himself as a ninja from what village?",
    "answers": [
      "Grass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) What is involved to use most summoning techniques?",
    "answers": [
      "blood"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Naruto) Who is the proctor for the second stage of the Chunin Exams?",
    "answers": [
      "Anko Mitarashi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Neon Genesis Evangelion)Who is the pilot of Unit-02?",
    "answers": [
      "asuka langley-soryu",
      "asuka langley soryu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Neon Genesis Evangelion) In what year did the show start airing?",
    "answers": [
      "1995"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(No Game No Life) How many races exist in Disboard?",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "sixteen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) What's the bounty on Roronoa Zoro's head?",
    "answers": [
      "120,000,000",
      "120000000"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Luffy ate what Devil Fruit?",
    "answers": [
      "Gomu Gomu",
      "gum gum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) What year was the manga created?",
    "answers": [
      "1997"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Who is the Pirate King?",
    "answers": [
      "Gol D. Roger",
      "Gol D Roger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) What did Sanji think Croccus was at the first time he saw him?",
    "answers": [
      "Flower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) What is Croccus' zodiac sign?",
    "answers": [
      "Gemini"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Which Baroque Works frontier agent was defeated first?",
    "answers": [
      "Miss Monday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Who in the fleet was the first to faint after meeting Dorry and Brogy?",
    "answers": [
      "Karoo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) What is Igaram's wife's name?",
    "answers": [
      "Teracotta"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Which Baroque Works officer agent has no special power from a devil fruit?",
    "answers": [
      "Miss Goldenweek"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Who is \"the child of demons\"?",
    "answers": [
      "Robin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Who has a goal of mapping the world?",
    "answers": [
      "Nami"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Who has a goal of wanting to discover the true history of the world?",
    "answers": [
      "Robin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Which character has a bounty under a pseudonym?",
    "answers": [
      "Usopp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Who is the navigator of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
    "answers": [
      "Nami"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) Whose crew did Nami work for before joining Luffy's crew?",
    "answers": [
      "Arlong",
      "Arlong's"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Piece) What fruit did Bartholomew Kuma eat?",
    "answers": [
      "Pawpaw fruit",
      "Pawpaw",
      "paw paw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Punch Man) Who is the main protagonist?",
    "answers": [
      "Saitama"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Punch Man) What city does Saitama live in?",
    "answers": [
      "Z-city",
      "z city",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Punch Man) What city is the headquarters of the Hero Association in?",
    "answers": [
      "A-city",
      "A city",
      "A"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(One Punch Man) Who is the Rank 1 Class S Hero?",
    "answers": [
      "Blast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Ouran High School Host Club) Who is mistaken for a boy in the anime?",
    "answers": [
      "Haruhi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Pokemon) In the original Japanese version, what is Ash Ketchum's name?",
    "answers": [
      "Satoshi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Pokemon) Pokemon was created by Stoshi Tajiri in which year?",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Pokemon) What starter pokemon did Ash Ketchum originally intend to choose?",
    "answers": [
      "Squirtle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Ranma 1/2) What does Ryouga turn into when he gets doused with cold water?",
    "answers": [
      "pig",
      "a pig"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Ranma 1/2) What is Ranma most afraid of?",
    "answers": [
      "cats",
      "cat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Rave Master) What's 3713 real name?",
    "answers": [
      "Elie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Usagi Tsukino is better known as...?",
    "answers": [
      "Sailor Moon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Sailor Moon) Who was Minako's crime-fighting alter ego before she became Sailor Venus?",
    "answers": [
      "sailor v"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Sailor Moon) What are the Sailor Senshi named after?",
    "answers": [
      "Planets"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Sailor Moon) Who is the love interest of Sailor Moon?",
    "answers": [
      "Tuxedo Mask",
      "Mamoru Chiba",
      "Mamoru",
      "Endymion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Shokugeki no Soma) Who is the 7th seat on the Elite Ten Council?",
    "answers": [
      "Satoshi Isshiki",
      "Isshiki"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Shokugeki no Soma) Who is the 10th seat on the Elite Ten Council?",
    "answers": [
      "Erina Nakiri",
      "Erina"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Shokugeki no Soma) What was Joichiro Yukihira's original name?",
    "answers": [
      "Joichiro Saiba",
      "Saiba Joichiro",
      "Saiba"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Shokugeki No Soma) What is the graduation rate at Totsuki Culinary Academy?",
    "answers": [
      "1%",
      "1",
      "One"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Shokugeki No Soma) What is the name of the Culinary Academy?",
    "answers": [
      "Totsuki Culinary Academy",
      "Totsuki"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Shokugeki No Soma) What is the term referring to a cooking duel allows students to settle debates and arguments?",
    "answers": [
      "shokugeki"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Slam Dunk) Sakuragi Hanamichi plays what position for Shohoku?",
    "answers": [
      "Power Forward"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What anime does Kurisu's online name reference?",
    "answers": [
      "Dragon Ball Z",
      "DBZ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is written on the Lab Members badge?",
    "answers": [
      "OSHMKUFA 2010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) Who does Mayuri work for?",
    "answers": [
      "Faris"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is Mayuri's favorite hobby?",
    "answers": [
      "Cosplay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) How old is Mayuri Shiina?",
    "answers": [
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) Who ate Kurisu's pudding?",
    "answers": [
      "Rintaro Okabe",
      "Rintaro",
      "Okabe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) How old is Rintaro Okabe?",
    "answers": [
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What will happen to Mayuri when Mayuri's pocket watch stops working?",
    "answers": [
      "Death",
      "Dies",
      "die",
      "She dies"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) Who is the sixth person that is shown in the opening?",
    "answers": [
      "Rintaro Okabe",
      "Rintaro",
      "Okabe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is the name of Okabe's Laboratory?",
    "answers": [
      "Future Gadget Laboratory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What name does Okabe call Kurisu?",
    "answers": [
      "Christina"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) In what area of Tokyo does Steins;Gate take place?",
    "answers": [
      "Akihabara"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) Why does Mayuri stay with Okabe?",
    "answers": [
      "She's his hostage",
      "Hostage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is Rintaro's landlord's name?",
    "answers": [
      "Yugo",
      "Mr Braun"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is Okabe's favorite drink?",
    "answers": [
      "Dk Pepper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) Steins;Gate is a collaboration work between 5pb. and who?",
    "answers": [
      "Nitro+"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What does the team call the text messages sent to the past?",
    "answers": [
      "Dmail",
      "d-mail"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What nickname does Rintaro give to Moeka?",
    "answers": [
      "Shining Finger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Steins;Gate) What is the name of the ability to retain memories across world lines?",
    "answers": [
      "Reading Steiner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maka Albarn is from what anime?",
    "answers": [
      "soul eater"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Sword Art Online) What is the second game Kirito goes into?",
    "answers": [
      "Alfheim Online",
      "Alfheim"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(The Last Airbender) What is the name of Aang's flying bison?",
    "answers": [
      "Appa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(The Last Airbender) What is the name of the evil prince that tries to capture Aang?",
    "answers": [
      "prince zuko",
      "zuko"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Trigun) What was Vash's brother called?",
    "answers": [
      "Knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sakura Kinamoto is the heroine of 'Cardcaptor Sakura'. In which CLAMP manga/anime does she also appear?",
    "answers": [
      "Tsubasa: Reservoir Chronicle",
      "Tsubasa",
      "Tsubasa Reservoir Chronicle",
      "Tsubasa - Reservoir Chronicle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Tsubasa Chronicle) What does the gang needed to collect?",
    "answers": [
      "Princess Sakura's feathers",
      "feathers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which manga made by CLAMP was named after a plant?",
    "answers": [
      "clover"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is name for the rabbit-like creatures from Clamp?",
    "answers": [
      "mokona"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Kazuki Takahashi best known as the creator of?",
    "answers": [
      "yu-gi-oh",
      "yu-gi-oh!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Yu Yu Hakusho) What level computer does Mitari have to fight in Game Master's territory?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "seven"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Yu Yu Hakasho) What is Yuskey's close advisor and ghost friend?",
    "answers": [
      "Botan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Zatch Bell) What color is Kyo's spell book?",
    "answers": [
      "red"
    ]
  },

    {
        "question": "In &quot;One Piece&quot;, who confirms the existence of the legendary treasure, One Piece?",
        "answers": ["Whitebeard"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure: Phantom Blood&quot; first released?",
        "answers": ["1987"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the final villain in the manga series &quot;Bleach&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Yhwach"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya&quot; series, the SOS Brigade club leader is unknowingly treated as a __ by her peers.",
        "answers": ["God"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime, &quot;Super Sonicio&quot;, what is Super Sonico&#039;s favorite food?",
        "answers": ["Macarons"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Fairy Tail&quot;, what is the nickname of Natsu Dragneel?",
        "answers": ["The Salamander"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the author of the manga series &quot;Astro Boy&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Osamu Tezuka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Little Witch Academia&quot;, what is Shiny Chariot&#039;s alias at Luna Nova Academy?",
        "answers": ["Ursula Callistis"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Super Dimension Fortress Macross first air?",
        "answers": ["1982"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Toriko&quot;, which food is knowingly compatible with Toriko?",
        "answers": ["Poison Potato"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the main protagonist of the fourth part of JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure?",
        "answers": ["Josuke Higashikata"]
    },
    {
        "question": "On what medium was &quot;Clannad&quot; first created?",
        "answers": ["Visual novel"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the main antagonist of the second part of JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure?",
        "answers": ["Kars"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The character Plum from &quot;No Game No Life&quot; is of what race?",
        "answers": ["Dhampir"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the 2012 animated film &quot;Wolf Children&quot;, what are the names of the wolf children?",
        "answers": ["Ame &amp; Yuki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the 2011 TV anime series, &quot;THE iDOLM@STER&quot;, what was the name of Iori&#039;s stuffed toy bunny?",
        "answers": ["Charles"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Krusty is the guild master of which guild in &quot;Log Horizon&quot;?",
        "answers": ["D. D. D", "DDD", "D.D.D", "D.D.D."]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the true moon princess in Sailor Moon?",
        "answers": ["Sailor Moon"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Satella in &quot;Re:Zero&quot; is the witch of what?",
        "answers": ["Envy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year did the manga &quot;Ping Pong&quot; begin serialization?",
        "answers": ["1996"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Jewelpet Sunshine&quot;, what is the song that plays when Kanon and her friends bust out of prison?",
        "answers": ["I Don&#039;t Want to Miss a Thing", "I Dont Want to Miss a Thing", "Don&#039;t Want to Miss a Thing", "Dont Want to Miss a Thing"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the &quot;Sailor Moon&quot; series, what is Sailor Jupiter&#039;s civilian name?",
        "answers": ["Makoto Kino"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animation studio animated &quot;Psycho Pass&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Production I.G"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The heroine of &quot;Humanity Has Declined&quot; is a mediator between humans and what?",
        "answers": ["Fairies"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; Manga was started in what year?",
        "answers": ["2006"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Highschool DxD&quot;, what is the name of the item some humans are born with?",
        "answers": ["Sacred Gear"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Junko Enoshima&#039;s imposter at the beginning of Danganronpa: Trigger Happy Havoc?",
        "answers": ["Mukuro Ikusaba"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime series &quot;Full Metal Alchemist&quot;, what do Alchemists consider the greatest taboo?",
        "answers": ["Human Transmutation"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In Digimon, what is the Japanese name for the final evolutionary stage?",
        "answers": ["Ultimate"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What animation studio produced &quot;Gurren Lagann&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Gainax"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did &quot;Attack on Titan&quot; Season 2 begin airing?",
        "answers": ["2017"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What studio animated Fullmetal Alchemist?",
        "answers": ["Bones"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The two main characters of &quot;No Game No Life&quot;, Sora and Shiro, together go by what name?",
        "answers": ["Blank"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What sport is being played in the Anime Eyeshield 21?",
        "answers": ["American Football"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animation studio animated &quot;To Love-Ru&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Xebec"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animation studio produced the anime adaptation of &quot;xxxHolic&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Production I.G"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Puella Magi Madoka Magica&quot;, what is the first name of Madoka&#039;s younger brother?",
        "answers": ["Tatsuya"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime, &quot;Full Metal Panel&quot;, who is Kaname&#039;s best friend?",
        "answers": ["Kyoko Tokiwa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Assassination Classroom what is the class that Korosensei teaches?",
        "answers": ["Class 3-E"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the colossal titan in &quot;Attack On Titan&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Bertolt Hoover"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the &quot;Toaru Majutsu no Index&quot; anime, Touma Kamijou is a level 0 esper with what ability?",
        "answers": ["Imagine Breaker"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animation studio animated the 2016 anime &quot;Mob Psycho 100&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Bones"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;A Certain Scientific Railgun&quot;, how many &quot;sisters&quot; did Accelerator have to kill to achieve the rumored level 6?",
        "answers": ["20,000", "20000", "20k"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In Dragon Ball Z, who was the first character to go Super Saiyan 2?",
        "answers": ["Gohan"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the armored titan in &quot;Attack On Titan&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Reiner Braun"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Noragami who is one of the main protagonists?",
        "answers": ["Yukine"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime &quot;Mr. Osomatsu&quot;, how many brothers does Osomatsu-san have?",
        "answers": ["5"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the corgi in Cowboy Bebop?",
        "answers": ["Einstein", "Ein"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the stuffed lion in Bleach?",
        "answers": ["Kon"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was given the title &quot;Full Metal&quot; in the anime series &quot;Full Metal Alchemist&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Edward Elric", "Ed Elric"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Toriko&quot;, what Heavenly King has an enhanced sense of Hearing?",
        "answers": ["Zebra"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What anime heavily features music from the genre &quot;Eurobeat&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Initial D"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is tje main protagonist of the fifth part of JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure?",
        "answers": ["Giorno Giovanna"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which studio animated Afro Samurai?",
        "answers": ["Gonzo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure, which character is able to accelerate time?",
        "answers": ["Enrico Pucci"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Highschool DxD&quot;, Koneko Toujou is from what race?",
        "answers": ["Nekomata"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did &quot;Attack on Titan&quot; first air?",
        "answers": ["2013"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created the animated movie &quot;Spirited Away&quot; (2001)?",
        "answers": ["Hayao Miyazaki", "Miyazaki Hayao"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the device that allows for infinite energy in the anime &quot;Dimension W&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Coils"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which manga did the &quot;404 Girl&quot; from 4chan originate from?",
        "answers": ["Yotsuba&amp;!", "Yotsuba"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the last line muttered in the anime film &quot;The End of Evangelion&quot;?",
        "answers": ["How disgusting"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;One Piece&quot;, what does &quot;the Pirate King&quot; mean to the captain of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
        "answers": ["Freedom"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;To Love-Ru: Darkness&quot;, which of the girls attempt to make a harem for Rito Yuuki?",
        "answers": ["Momo Deviluke"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the ADV (English) Dub of the anime &quot;Ghost Stories&quot;, which character is portrayed as a Pentacostal Christian?",
        "answers": ["Momoko Koigakubo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Akatsuki&#039;s subclass in &quot;Log Horizon&quot; is what?",
        "answers": ["Tracker"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the age of Ash Ketchum in Pokemon when he starts his journey?",
        "answers": ["10"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did &quot;Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon&quot; air in Japan?",
        "answers": ["1992"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Inuyasha&quot;, what are the heroes are looking to collect?",
        "answers": ["Jewel Shards"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Medaka Kurokami from &quot;Medaka Box&quot; has what abnormality?",
        "answers": ["The End"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The manga JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure is split into how many parts?",
        "answers": ["9"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aoi Miyamori is the production manager of what anime in &quot;Shirobako&quot;?",
        "answers": ["The Third Aerial Girls Squad", "Third Aerial Girls Squad"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the stands from &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure&quot; mimics the likeness of a tomato?",
        "answers": ["Pearl Jam"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Black Lagoon&quot;, what colour is Rock&#039;s tie?",
        "answers": ["Teal"]
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the first episode of Soul Eater released?",
        "answers": ["2008"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In Ms. Kobayashi&#039;s Dragon Maid, who is Kobayashi&#039;s maid?",
        "answers": ["Tohru"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the school in the anime and manga &quot;Gosick&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Saint Marguerite", "St. Marguerite", "St Marguerite"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Ash Ketchum&#039;s second Pokemon?",
        "answers": ["Caterpie"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did the anime &quot;Himouto! Umaru-chan&quot; air?",
        "answers": ["2015"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the &quot;Dragon Ball&quot; franchise, what is the name of Goku&#039;s brother?",
        "answers": ["Raditz"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animation studio produced the first season of &quot;Log Horizon&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Satelite"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;A Certain Magical Index,&quot; what is Accelerator able to control?",
        "answers": ["Vectors"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which studio animated Soul Eater?",
        "answers": ["Bones"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, how many Trans-weapons were created?",
        "answers": ["3"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What song plays in the ending credits of the anime &quot;Ergo Proxy&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Paranoid Android"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What studio animated Ouran High School Host Club?",
        "answers": ["Bones"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Hunter x Hunter&quot;, what are members in Killua&#039;s family known for being?",
        "answers": ["Assassins"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;To Love-Ru&quot;, who is the first to hear of Yami&#039;s past from her?",
        "answers": ["Rito"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ikki Kurogane is known by what nickname at the beginning of &quot;Chivalry of a Failed Knight&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Worst One"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was studio Trigger&#039;s first original long-form animated series for television?",
        "answers": ["Kill la Kill"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year does Part 7 of &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure&quot; take place in?",
        "answers": ["1890"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;To Love-Ru&quot;, Ren and Run are from what planet?",
        "answers": ["Memorze"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the &quot;Re:Zero&quot; manga series, which of the following Sin Archbishops eats Rem&#039;s existence?",
        "answers": ["Ley Batenkaitos"]
    },
    {
        "question": "&quot;Silhouette&quot;, a song performed by the group &#039;KANA-BOON&#039; is featured as the sixteenth opening of which anime?",
        "answers": ["Naruto Shippuden"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animation studio produced &quot;Sword Art Online&quot;?",
        "answers": ["A-1 Pictures"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the last name of Edward and Alphonse in the Fullmetal Alchemist series.",
        "answers": ["Elric"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Future Diary&quot;, what is the name of Yuno Gasai&#039;s Phone Diary?",
        "answers": ["Yukiteru Diary"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Seven Deadly Sins what is the name of one of the sins?",
        "answers": ["Diane"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In &quot;Shakugan no Shana&quot; what was the Shana usually referred as?",
        "answers": ["Flame-Haired Burning-Eyed Hunter"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animation studio animated &quot;Hidamari Sketch&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Shaft"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2013, virtual pop-star Hatsune Miku had a sponsorship with which pizza chain?",
        "answers": ["Dominos"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which song was the callsign for Stefan Verdemann&#039;s KWFM radio station in Urasawa Naoki&#039;s &quot;Monster&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Over the Rainbow"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The character Momonga from the &quot;Overlord&quot; series orders his servants to call him by what name?",
        "answers": ["Ainz Ooal Gown"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the creator of the manga series &quot;One Piece&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Eiichiro Oda"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character of the anime &quot;One-Punch Man&quot;?",
        "answers": ["Saitama"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the 9th Pokemon movie, who is the Prince of the Sea?",
        "answers": ["Manaphy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Black Butler, who is betrothed to be married to Ciel Phantomhive?",
        "answers": ["Elizabeth Midford"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What caused the titular mascot of Yo-Kai Watch, Jibanyan, to become a yokai?",
        "answers": ["Being run over by a truck"]
    }
]